From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, true
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like we awake and step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like we awake and don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream be the colon and slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Boom, set into the night.
Panel looking sideways, someone's gotta fight.
Producers on mute, praying this don't spike.
Diamond's feeling spicy, shirt slipping down low.
Oops, she says, with a wink.
That's the whole show.
Sigh's half asleep, but still cracking.
Spunky and Nick Johnson, we got Spunky and Jamie are both members and Mods. Wow.
Double team. Okay. Let's see what else.
Samantha Avery Mod. Hello, Nick Johnson. I'll make Nick a mod again.
He's a good mod. It's just like I forgot to do it.
How's everybody? We have, if summer comes and wants to do the pan, her panel,
we can do her open panel. Otherwise,
open for one-on-one. Hey, Sponky, how are you? Yeah, sorry, I fell asleep a little bit earlier.
I was kind of a little bit sleepy, but I did, uh, you know, I had a nice dinner. I went
to bed, but hey, Prairie. Hi, sweet. How are you? I hope you had fun. Oh, yeah, it's
to kind of nod off a little bit. You're doing well. Good. I'm doing good. I'm wearing my regular
but uh and this morning I like had an order of like a bunch of like I just stuff like you know
I got uh some like some like floor moderates or air freshener it's really good actually this air
freshener is so good this is the real this is the real shit you have to get this stuff
Okay, it's fresh.
How are you? Yeah, so I hope you like the thing. Okay, so I've been used for you people to see
Let me know if they'd like something I don't know what they look like, okay, so I can't really like
Tell I can't really design a card, but if it only looks like that. Okay, so spunky and
Jamie
Nick
You all get a card
No, I mean, I'm gonna make it. I'm gonna decide a tarot card with you on it. I
Know she does it cuz he gets a card to sheets the card that a lot of people do I already have a page in a beta
But no, no, you think it might have to be
I was trying to do, I was trying to make you see that I kept getting the dog wrong. You want to see your card? Yeah.
Um, yeah, just we might make, just we might, just we might be on the show.
So wait and see.
He's surprised, he doesn't have, he pissed me off that day.
I'll just make you a queen.
Well, you'll be a queen. Yeah.
Jamie, okay, yeah, Jamie will be the, I have to make a mod card for Jamie.
I don't know, who's the high priestess?
Well, I mean, I need to redo it.
They can look more like you, but yeah,
that's a good prototype, I think.
Well, you know what's funny is like,
if you see the page in the video,
the page in the music video,
like when they're like, paste, you know,
but the page in the Sims, right?
There's a little bit of a line like that, right?
Hold on, I'm just shooting down, sorry.
So,
The girl that video looks like she looks like a she looks like Joker's drawing a page. She has red hair
It's just like my looking good. I don't know
Okay
Okay, I really got a little warm brothers. That's all folks
Yeah, so that'll be cool
Guys, I don't really will they'll be kind of like a panel verse they get might be very niche
Extremely nice. I can't call it YouTube deck. I can call it I can call it videos like live streamer deck or something
I don't know it has kind of a panel. It's like my AI knows that I'm
Obsessed with like, you know
You know, I'm showing stuff and like I'm like what like
So it's what they're just panels into everything
Okay, that's right. I'm gonna say that Randall. I want to say hi. Yeah
Otherwise, though, but it's only one on one right now Randall. So the panel is open sponsorship
Unless summer comes then it's her panel
Well, oh here we go
Hey homo, you're doing it again man, did you ever listen to yourself stream you're blabbing you're not even saying nothing
We can't
No, you just don't make any sense
Okay, I don't know. I mean, I don't know if you're stoned. Why I speak English. I mean
My microphone was all the way up, I didn't see it wasn't
You can't it's like, you know, yeah, you don't have to yell at me. I'm sorry
Okay, you're right. If you're gonna help me then, you know, okay. Thank you
Fair enough, but we're all calm, bro. Everything is okay. All right. Just articulate your words a little better, please
I mean, you're just
You could have hear me I was go talking about hearing listen, I hear you
Just want you to rewind to listen how you sound. I'm not saying you're stupid. I can't hear the microphone is maybe not
That's powerful. I'm not you know, you're just like I'm not stuttering. I'm talking
Okay, I think you're gaslighting me
I'm literally not though, but you are exactly you know, you don't know fucking lie to you
No, of course not, but it's like I think YouTube's frying your brain a little bit
Okay, it's it's it's not working. Okay. Bye
Oh well, yeah, I mean it's like
I mean it's like you can say it there's a nice way to say things right if my microphone was all the way up
Maybe I was talking fast. Maybe and you need to enunciate more, but you don't say it like it shows not working and all this kind of stuff
It shows working just fine
Don't throw that shit on me, okay
Really funny random guy you're really cool
Sometimes I wish instead of like stories about people people eating cats. I wish there were some humans the cats would eat
I'm sure it's okay
We can say the same okay guys. I'm getting five. I mean I think five or six minutes. Oh, I got like 24 25 bucks
I got like meaning like five or six more decks including the Christina Ricci deck is called cat full of spiders
I don't know if you see that looks pretty cool
I'll see if I can see it right here.
Let me see.
Yeah, it's Cat Pull Spider, it's this deck right here.
I don't mean to say, that's a really,
I don't know if it's like on sale or something, but.
Yeah, I heard your cat.
Your cat's sweet.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're lucky. You're lucky. You're lucky to have the cat. Oh, I guess the cats lucky to have you too
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm mad
Can you hear me? Okay? I'm sorry. I'll speak louder
This I'm so comfortable with you guys. I just see if you can relax away
But yeah, maybe I do babble and stuff. It's hard to also talk for a long period of time
You don't want to hear me talk you can sponsor a panel and then I'll shut up and sit in the back for a little bit, okay?
I'm doing my best, see, nails are better.
Did you hear, yeah, hello, hello, hello.
Hello, hello.
Okay, let's do a reading with a collective.
I'll just do quick three cards.
So guys, is anybody on TikTok?
So guys, it's really cool.
So here's what's happening on TikTok.
I'm just getting like a million people like not a million people follow me
but like a lot it's like it's just like I think I have like four hundred five
hundred people following me already and I mean actually it's I only think two
I have 250 following me and then I'm following like 500 that's that's right
okay so anyway it's hey okay thank you thank you appreciate that yeah that's
We're given we're given
Yeah, so where was I yeah, so
Thank you random guy you're a cool guy, okay
Yeah, it's the end of the day people you know
Support me. I know really if you fuck with me, so thank you. Okay
So, yeah, pretty cool, I think it might be the real deck too.
Yeah, but anyway, so I'm getting some more cards.
I'll pull some for the chat, I'll use a cat deck right now.
I mean, I'm trying to,
maybe I'll get some more cat cards,
but it's like, I keep like,
I have this deck of cat cards now,
and so I'm like, oh, that's enough cat cards,
but it is caro and cats,
so I suppose I could deal with some more, but.
I love these. These are the cute, cute artistry on these though. They look like pushkin. You know, if you ever see the pushkin cat or the
second Japanese
stuff cat
But these are cool because they're like kind of like in the style of the writer and so it's like they're easily recognizable
But they're really in a cute little cat slime
Okay, so
Let's see, what's the message for the chat?
The chat needs to know, I'll pull three cards
with a message and then a word of advice with a message, okay.
Oh, okay, that one pops out.
What's first?
Four of Cups, okay.
One of Cups is boredom, you know?
Look, he's bored and he's finished
with all those cups of coffee, but then he has another cup.
This is like a really good copy.
That's like a Starbucks in there.
And so he's gonna be happy. Okay, so he's he made those himself. He's getting the Starbucks the golden cup, right?
Yo, let's take that. I'm just playing a few cards for this chat. Let me see here
Okay, okay, so we have to pull so dissatisfaction with something but then I
Something handed to you that's gonna make you much more passionate. Okay. Okay. Here's and you've been waiting for this actually, too
Okay. Oh, it looks strength
Yeah, the strength look at the little cat is like, you know, people to hand that big lion just by like, you know
Just being nice and soft and gentle not like trying to like hurt the lion or chase the line around, right?
Being very gentle and the lines like oh, I'm a little head massage. Oh, it feels good. He's just sitting there
It's like, you know, so, you know, you get more flies with the honey than you do with vinegar
Okay
Third up king of swords. Maybe time. You know, this is a very intelligent decisive good communicator guy
Look, what does he have? He's a little dog
He's a little dog
Duggy
Yeah, and first oh look at the oh my god. Is that real? Oh, no, it's not good
Okay, anyway emperors on his throne. He has a sword, you know, he has all the power of the kings
He has the whole actually the whole realm. He has the you know the dog
So the dog must be powerful companion, right? Also looks like there's some kind of harvest involved in this somehow. Okay
One more one more
Um advice nine of tentacles advice is just like go out enjoy the abundance of the world
Look if there's buttons all around us because like I don't necessarily in his pocket right there
It's just all around right it's like and so and then he's happy and
The birds flying up is just a magical world right mountains
Mountains touching grass and very expensive hat not wearing pants, but you know, that's a cat you can forgive them for that and
There you go. I mean basically just enjoy enjoy life and enjoy life and the beauty and the abundance of the real wealth of the world
Which is like the beauty of it, right?
There we go. Oh, six six six. Are you giving us satanic subliminals Nick? Yeah, six six six Bob Bob Bob the Hebrew letter
Dematria
Know all about it. Yep. Oh nothing. It's like a trident upside down
They kind of like you know, which is like a pitchfork a trident associate with King Neptune also associated with you know
Throwing things away
Okay
Hey, maybe oh you got the leopard. Okay. This is associated with leopard mind control cult system MP ultra
This is the sex kitten beta programming. Everybody in chat is now attracted to, you know, cat-like women in their early 20s.
Okay.
Okay. What is that? Okay.
Ah!
I don't know what is I don't know any guesses anybody. I know I can't have them turn on the microphone again
I don't want to go Jeff
It's up for you side. How are you?
Dear Lord
Yeah, well, yeah, but the bar is low, but you set the bar Ram guy I said it kind of high you kind of like you know
If I'm Pokemon or the Pikachu who is that is that a Pokemon is a Pikachu character or Pikachu is a Pokemon character
I mean as a what is the genus and the species anyone know oh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't touch poke. Don't touch the genitals. It's perverted. Okay guys. Come on
Hopefully your friends have got gasoline
I'm I'm no I don't even know gas gas like it only like gas I have is what you know that we day smoke, right?
Yeah, Alistair you know a famous Alistair Crowley quote is never been anyone says I suck like which they do all the time
Everyone says I always say the stuff his quote was I was born to suck
Hey, Genesis
And appearance and personal uh, no, it's not really does not really want to the same
Because of course you're not gonna you're not really your true self on the panel
I mean that maybe you are as much as you can just like I am as much as I can but in the world
We present a social mask called a persona
Everyone wears one just part of the being human body in itself is kind of mask
Kind of a meat suit, you know
We're gonna use it for a period it gets old like a car, right and that breaks down
We're good. Maybe we get a new car
for bad who will be
Probably walking around somewhere for a while, but I have faith that we'll all get well all eventually
Okay, we're supposed to be you know, hopefully it will be
More positive than negative. You're all you in a panel. It's okay. Everyone would say but no, it's a no
It's then that's just in psychology is called the there's like the persona
Which is like how you present yourself in the public and so it's almost impossible if you're if you're being observed if you're great
You know then it's possible to be yourself because you're you modify
You just changes who you are like that's why different people together make different
Combinations that's why they make your group makes a whole like egregore, right?
Okay, so I'm sorry if I'm being long-winded though, or it's I'm really into you know
Not as much segment for it is Carl you
And he has a book called the red book. I
Was speaking I'm not speaking in broken riddles. What are you? What it's a kind of basic psychology
I know maybe are you more into sales though? You're more into things to say. Oh, hold on. Oh, well
Okay, Nick just show me his dick. I think I think so
Not speaking in broken riddles. I mean, I'm not some kind of like sinks. I like to like
But if it is a riddle, maybe you should try to figure it out. They're not broken with broken riddles
I don't think you can be figured out. There's not enough information
Okay
Maybe you're speaking to me and broken riddles if you're thinking about that you're and then you say I'm doing it is
Some people are taking cute people what they're doing
It's a projection
So I try not to accuse is your cues is that cues?
So let me see
It's like I'm trying to save you from sounding like a homeless man on skid row
Where's the link for people could crash out yeah, it's one at a time of course right now until the panel
It's summer can open the panel though. She she has the sponsorship in her
In that bag
Summer gets a card random guy. You don't get a card easy. I don't know about I don't know. I just don't know
Maybe I think I'll put easy on a card. Yeah, I can be easy on a card
Who else time maybe I'll put me I'll make a time card
Hello
Thank you
I have to go to a certain area like no like fortune area just to get service
Good reception. Okay. Well, how are you doing? Yes?
I'm doing all right doing all right though, right? Um, you know that I don't want to come up here
So you know that shoulder we were talking about earlier. Okay. Yeah, that's a good now
Do it, which you put the one posting the videos with me and stuff
Yeah, the one for the video is me you yeah one one of her pages got to be down, but in that how you
Good I had they had a nice dinner and did I see the flirty day freak off in voice chat
Oh, so flirty up flirty diamonds
He's careless work
Yeah, she's in she's in like careless kids like this court voice chat like her region demon are having
Stuff like that. Like it was it was intense if you don't want to watch some gay some gay porn, you know
You can go try to find that somewhere, but I'm not
I mean, I just I haven't seen that I just seen 48 30 diamond, you know, it's boobs about 10 times
But I've never seen like anything else
I kind of like I kind of like I remember they know I'm really not in the freak-offs
I leave when they start as soon as I see boobs
I'm I gotta have to I bail
Backstage, you know taking photos and stuff like that because there's people people are always back stage
Like you're playing like the backstage stuff like I'm from the other night and then it's like but I was listening to that anyway
It's why I heard that conversation. It's that it's funny. No, maybe it should be no
I shouldn't say that I should let people like just like, you know, think that it's safe back there, but
People should figure out already because you know, you know people's boobs and buttholes are already
I don't the internet from being backstage and so just be careful what you show
Look at Nick. Oh, hold on. What's going on here? Oh
That's how you get on the show
Yeah, but then I was like, I'm not really it's like it's like people's personalities if it's like it's too much
I don't care what they look like
I know I've never I've never I've never seen you naked. I've never seen you naked
But I ain't going kisses or take a I know no guy guy guy guys guys he never
that's like his signature thing, will your name get on that lamp, you're famous to him
I don't want the name of the lamp because that, oh it says Nick there because that means like shade
you know it's like a lamp shade and so that means like no no no he supports everybody in his lamp
he looks at it and rotates and tells us sure he does okay hold me
yeah he does it right now and I need to look at it
Let's say let's say you know the people on Freddy Krueger's like belly that he all the souls that he ate
It's like a very uncomfortable in there. Okay. I don't want to be out. I know thank you, Nick
Okay, thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Bye. Okay. I
Don't know
Well, he can go sponsored in his show because you know
I'm where I'm busy enough trying to get my own sponsorships
He's he's literally jerking off back said now he just smells his hand. Okay. Yes, hand on his pants. Now he's spelling it. Okay
Okay, whatever
No, I can watch I can watch him play again. I can watch him flex from backstage
I don't I don't when I like like one time he like showed me showed his butt on the camera another time he showed his
He said no, he's just like putting his hand on his pants. It's like, you know, but you know, it's okay
He's a he's shy. He's afraid. He's afraid. I'll take a picture of him. I wouldn't do that. Come on. Are you taking his pieces of the recording?
Put your hands up. Put your hands up. Put your hands up. Put your hands up. Put your hands up. Put your hands up.
You got to show them both your hands next to your face or on your head. And then he's going to show you comment.
No, he will. Oh, good. Oh, yeah. He's coming out. Oh, my God. Okay. Okay.
Oh, see, I told you that.
No, it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's just a pair of flesh colored nunchucks.
What the hell? Oh, yeah
I know they made this in flesh
Yeah, anyway
Anyway
Okay
No worries
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, just just Nick like doing some karate or something like that
Okay, I don't know it's like I think like a lot like I don't know it's a not
Like a lot of people are like I'll leave you the show or anything
But I just think there's a big misunderstanding about about the that the clapping system and the and maybe that's the panel system
And so if you are if people are your questions about it
I put it all in the I put it all the description of the video of the channel and so you can see the instructions
It's very simple. It's just like one sentence for each each thing
It's very simple instructions versus your cut and dry and so and it's not know it's not everybody gets charged
It's just one person can sponsor the panel
And, you know, and they get control of the banner for like, you know, the, while their show is going on, which is like pretty good advertisement.
There's people that, you know, you have a TTS plate for like $5, you know, it's like, so it's like, it's not too different from that because you get the banner.
So you get the message out longer even. I'll even read it. There you go. Okay. So if you're interested, if you do have a channel.
I'm saying, I'm saying we have a new chat site. Yeah, I'm just, I'm talking to you and I'm going to talk to you.
I'll join the chat when I go back to the trap
Well, that's very quiet that there's a Trevor person the people were saying was you but I don't believe that to you
And I repeat go around when I met on
That's not me that is not me I got a leg of the easy cameras on the recording and that's it
It looks like that that that that Harry Potter that
That that was I forgot it mouth blisters. I don't I don't know that
Yeah, you mouth boy. Yeah, the evil the evil blond person
Yeah
Albino, okay, let's see either has your flow states panel. Okay, and then you know so
Okay, so yeah, well, it's good if it people on panels like I was you know, I'm I'm not I wasn't on a panel last night
I was just in chats
Watching like reading what people were saying
Vita was on for like 15 16 hours today. Wow. That's pretty pretty good pretty epic. I think
My longest trim is maybe 18 hours, but I did sleep
No, you did 24 hours of it, but be did the great last night. Oh
Yeah, I mean with Alexander was on you like Alexander or not or do you know Alexander that was funny
I was loving that part was you like Alex I
He said he's gonna kick it away with a lot of stuff.
But Alexander, the lady, but yeah, Alice,
I saw him, she kicked him off, she kicked him off,
and then Bray, she's like, oh, this is the evil acts
of the good allies, and then Alexander fell asleep
on her panel last night, that was kind of funny.
All right, yeah.
It's okay, it happened to me one time, you know?
It happens to me, I was on my panel,
so I don't judge, this is funny, you know?
No, anyway, yeah
So, I don't know it's a second. What am I doing my 24 hours stream?
I mean you guys want to do that. I mean it's like you really can't do like I mean I can do two 12 hours
But I think once it's over 12 hours. They just cut out the end of the stream like they got up anything after 12 hours
They don't they don't put it down. I don't think
So it's kind of like, I don't want to lose, I do a 24 hour footage, but 24 hours.
I don't know. Do you guys want me to do it? If you guys have suggestions, you know,
if you sponsor something, I'll probably do a lot of things.
If they hit the like system, the donation system, the share system, why not?
Why not give them what they want?
Give them what they want and they'll give you what you want.
Well, again, that's like, you know, that's like, you know, it's like, I'll rub your back,
you rub my back, you know, it's like, and then everybody gets the massage, right?
And it's like, then, you know, it's like, there we go.
Also get to give and receive which is like it's good. It's better to give and receive than just give then receive, right?
It's like, you know, it's better. I think it's good to like put out put out things and it's lucky to receive
I see it as a fair trade. I see it as a fair trade. I give y'all what y'all do.
Oh, yeah, you know, there's a lot of people that's watching right now. They will not
put dear life, not go live.
Oh, no, no.
They will sit there in their house and they will wait for the next person to be like live.
So why not look out for y'all if y'all look up for us?
Okay, oh it's 24 hours stream. So maybe on maybe on Sunday or something
I could start like midnight on Saturday night, and then like something goes through to Monday night. Maybe I look at this
Hold on look at that. We are out here. Oh my god
Mickey boys stop flexing like that for him
They're gonna eat on the street never be backstage in a couple seconds
I'm trying to chill
I let him up for a second, he flexed, and then that's it.
People used to donate a lot of money for our streets.
Okay, that would be a good publicity thing.
Maybe I'll do the whole thing at my speedo, and then I'll get all,
I'll buy a bunch of food and stuff, so I have everything I need.
Someone's still here, bro. Someone's still here. You still could go.
I oh, yeah, I know some summer in the chat, but I want she said she wants to do her panel when she
Okay, oh summertime. Oh, yeah, so yeah, it's still summertime summer time. Yeah, well, it's almost it's a crew
Is it almost over? It's the July we're right in the middle
I think right now is the considered dog days of summer like and that's because serious is the closest to earth that will be all year
I think it's mid-summer. We're mid-summer right now.
Mid-summer, okay.
Yeah, and if you saw the movie Mid-Summer, that's another good cult film.
It's by the same guy that did Hereditary.
It's about this girl that goes on vacation with her boyfriend.
She's having a lot of mental problems and stuff to go to this vacation in Sweden or something,
and it's like this little commune where they have all their own traditions
and start bringing the people into the traditions, and some of them are very...
I'll say okay. It's very occultist. So it's an interesting movie take out mid-summer if you haven't seen it
It's a pretty scary movie too. Hey guys, is that my shirt? Look at that. I got a new shirt
Hold on
I'm gonna fill up a full screen once again
Cute see it. I like it. I like it. It's a skeleton. I'm kissing the cat
It looks like Lola because it looks like my cat Lola. So
Yeah, but that was kind of cute people usually. Yeah, so yeah, I'll see if if anyone has any other ideas of
Streams we can do of or like, you know things we can I get you know
I'm basically I'm at a beach city, but I'm in Los Angeles. I can get places
You know as long as I can like, you know, I can get you know
I was telling you lots of right, but some of the panels are good like donation with this
Um, the speedo idea, you know, you need to catch a good one, dude.
Yeah, I can do like stuff like, you know, IRL, IRL, I can do some IRL stuff, but, uh, yeah, um, yeah, I plan on doing that and more stuff, but it's like, but it's like, you know, and I don't want to, I don't want to do anything like.
Thank you, of course permanent like I would not think I mean elder ones offer me a hundred dollars to save my eyebrows
I was like no because it's like I was just so too weird as though it's like, you know, I would have but you know
I'll do unreasonable things. I don't I don't want to eat anything weird. I don't know. So there's people there's a
YouTube channel called RDRR like hardy-har-har and it's a bunch of black guys
They're and they take like a wheel and they spin the wheel and it's just like the most disgusting like
They put on wigs and dance and pretend to be women and like they have the dumbest dares
But people are there they're like donating like money all night for them to do these stupid dares
They get into wigs and just act gay. It's like so dumb, but it's it's kind of funny
Matter of fact, that's what you should get. You should get the wheel
Not you do it book attenders do it
Yeah, well, yeah, I can have different kind of stuff. Yeah, Christine was here earlier actually a ghost hunting stream
Well, it's like okay, so I do live in a haunted city like redondo is a hot like pretty haunted city
There's stuff around here
And you know South Bay in general Los Angeles is a very haunted place. There's a bunch of indian burial grounds stuff around here
Yeah, but goes hunting. Yeah, but it's like, you know
It's funny when Benny does it, because I watch Benny do anything, but I don't know, what would I do?
I just walk around with one of those, those little, like, specific tests, the sonar, or whatever, in the air, or the EVP.
Yeah, I like his voice. I mean, I have a bunch of ghost apps. I have a bunch of ghost hunting apps. I mean, it's like like a ghost radar. There's one called ghost radar. There's different ones. And, you know, it's, they say weird things sometimes, but it's like, sometimes it doesn't make that much sense, you know, but I do like some of the TV shows, but most of them are pretty faked. It'd be cool. Okay.
That goes stuff. Okay. Are you your British time? I think British people like ghosts a lot, right?
And then see that Christine was here just a spirit box. Yeah, I like the spirit boxes. I have a
I did have some cool apps, but I don't know if I have them anymore. I mean, I can look at my Google store
Let's see ghosts some of them are pretty good
They always will start going off immediately a practically. Let me see ghost radar
I watch the ghost things hearing there, but it doesn't treat me when when you actually see or hear something weird
Oh
No, when you hear like a whisper or something like that. I've heard whispers and shit like that
So
Okay, yeah
There was a video I saw of
this guy he's like look at the TV set and it was like there was like a smudge on
the TV but it was in this like perfect shape of like a clown space like
laughing it was like you had to look closely and he was like he was like he
was saying it was a demon and stuff that came through the this like this like
piece of I don't know whatever it was there this piece of oh it's just a reflection of the TV
Oh I saw a video on the day I was shooting y'all right?
Not on the day I was shooting y'all.
Somebody on Instagram the other day some guy was laying down in bed. He looked in the mirror
There was a witch looking like witch just moving left and right on me
And he was a your the fucking name put the camera to the side check and show everybody
And then he went under the bed and then went back in the mirror and the bitch is gone
Some of those I mean so many most of those videos are fakes
I've made now that I've seen them like with like the eyes of like, you know, I watch some of the old ones
You're right
Yeah
Most of them they take out to talk both boy it goes hiding videos and it's just like they have so many it's like that
Oh, like every day they're saying like ghosts and they're they're materializing and there's special
I mean it's kind of obvious some people are better at the effects than other people some are convincing
I like what they do to do these videos on dolls and the dolls like slowly moves throughout the night. That's kind of
On the watch
Then you
You actually have to pause play pause play record pause play record pause play report and adjust all that
You know saying there'll be a glitch between at least somewhere somebody can find that glitch. But anyway, yeah
um based on this conversation we have it now psyche you believe
past videos of ghost interactions is more realistic than
The now and days
How long has the photoshop been around so we have photoshop, okay? We have photoshop
But then it's like even going back ten years
Yeah, okay, but then and then we had regular cameras which they had like double exposures and stuff like that
It happened
But even like the double exposures can happen on the old-style cameras even though it's like you know what they had like
You know they take like half hour to take the picture and stuff like that the old the first camera
Okay, so my old-school camera. What's up with the camera? Oh, you take a picture of it and it prints it out right there
What about those? They can't see the moment.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Polaroids. There you go. The Polaroid that catches a goat at the scene at the moment.
If it's a Polaroid, but it's a Polaroid, but if it's, you know, if it's authenticated,
like, you know, this came out of the camera, but it's like, there's still like things with
heat. You can do the Polaroid that can do things. There's like, there's different,
especially, you know, who knows about this stuff as photographers. And so they would be able to,
like, you know, easily kind of like, you know, add a plate or like, you know, I mean, there's ways to,
there's people that have forged the Mona Lisa. So it's not going to be too hard to forge, you know,
You know, you know anything can be have a convincing copy, right? So
But they you know the money they say they tell you how many strokes you actually prevent them
Hope to make that photo right so the dedicated they have to get one of those people to
Well, it's just always, I mean, basically it was like not even, it's been copied and
stuff like that.
They have fakes, but it's like...
Oh yeah, fake copies.
There are hundreds and thousands of fakes.
But it's like, but usually it's in the museum, but it has been stolen before.
And so that's when people, I think, would come forward with fake copies.
Or, you know, it's like...
I'll take the one.
I'll call it to...
What do we call it?
Josephina. Oh, Josephina, okay. Yeah. Well, at least I'm Josephine. Someday I'll read
you about the Empress Theodoria and just, just, just, just Sineas, just Sineas. Yeah,
someday I'll read you that story if you want to hear about some ancient intrigue in the
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
So this is like this book was like the empty
This ancient like one of the first they kind of like tell all books they kind of an expose. Let me see. It's like
Let's call it. Let me see you
Dora
Justina
Exposed a I mean and it was called
See
Okay, it's called the Secret History by Procopius.
Okay, so by Procopius, and so I'll read some of it.
So this is the Secret History by Procopius.
And so if you wanna know about,
like this is like the Byzantine Empire,
so this is like the Empress, her name was Theodora.
Okay, and then she had there's the emperor was Justin. Okay, so she was emperors
Yeah
It was in Constantinople and Turkey and stuff in Byzantine Empire, but she was born around 495 AD
Her father was a bit. Okay, so her father was a bear keeper. Okay, I'll go through it. So hold on so it goes
Okay, so secret history
Okay, history. So this is like one of the first like kind of like trashy
Like it would have been like, you know, he didn't get printed until after he died
All right, because it would be too dangerous
So it's a procopious. Okay, my procopious secret history procopious
It's really interesting book that you I think you'll find it interesting because it's like it kind of reads well today
Well, this is like yeah, this is like this is supposedly true like this was the history, okay, so
Anybody and everything I can see
And if my my grandparents or whatever like I thought it's my own two eyes. It's history. I believe it
But anything other than that I can't believe in my time. Okay, if it's not my time, I never I really don't believe it
But I listen to it. Don't give me wrong
Yeah
So, okay guys by the way, you can
Okay, so this is kind of hard race. This is like one of these
original it was published see but it's also published way way way way is you know
When did the guys think about this? When did the printing press get invented in like 1500 around there or something like that so?
Well, where are all these books that are you know, they were supposedly written before they were there just on scrolls or something like that
And I know they're all missing because the Alexandria library
Resets yeah, that's heard about the recess. Yeah
I'm skeptical a little bit. It just seems like kind of like it goes like along with the flat earth people
They kind of talk about the same stuff. Okay, that tablet is dying. I need to plug this
I
Have the book but I don't I can't we go find it right after I'm gonna look for the internet book
Okay, so I know it was on like a website for free. So let me see
Okay, okay, okay, okay, so I think this might be good
Okay, this is for project buton bro. Here. This is perfect. Okay, so read now. Okay, so it says
I'll just read the first I'll read the chapter. I'll skip the introduction because chapter one
Okay chapter one says okay
The wife of
Belia Seris, who I have spoken of in my previous writings,
was the daughter and granddaughter of chariot drivers,
men who had practiced their art in the circus
at Byzantium and Thelausonica.
Her mother was one of the prostitutes of the theater.
She herself at first lived a lewd life,
giving herself up to unbridled debauchery.
Besides this, she devoted herself to the study of the drugs,
which had long been used in her family,
and learned the properties of those
which were essential for carrying out her plans.
At last, she was betrothed and married to Belisarius, although she had already borne many children.
She formed adulterous connections as soon as she was married, which took pains to conceal
the fact by making use of familiar artifices, not out of any respect for her husband, for
she never felt any shame or any crime or whatever, and hidweakened him by enchantments.
But because she dreaded the vengeance of the Empress, Pertheodora was very bitter against
but after she had made Theodora her humble friend by helping her win in the greatest difficulties,
first of all by making a way with silverias, as shall be told hereafter, and afterward by
ruining John of Cappadocia, as I have already described, she became less timid and scorning
all concealments, shrank from no kind of wickedness. There was a Thracian youth named Theodosius
in the household of Belisarius, who was by descent one of the Unomian faith.
On the eve of his departure for Libya, Belasarius held the youth over the font, received him
into his arms after baptism, and therefore made him a member of his household with the
consent of his wife, according to the Christian Rite of Adoption.
Antonina, therefore, received theodosius as the son consecrated by religion, and in consequence
loved him, paid him special attention, and obtained complete dominion over him.
Afterwards, during this voyage, she became madly enamored of him, and, beside being herself
Being beside herself with passion cast away all fear of everything human or divine
Together with all traces of modesty and enjoyed him at first and secret
Afterwards even in the presence of her servants and handmaidens for she was by this time so mad with lust
That what she was disregarded everything that stood in the way of her passion
Once when they were at Carthage, Belisarius caught her in the act, but permitted himself to be deceived by his wife.
He found them both together in an underground chamber and was furiously enraged at the site,
but she showed him no sign of fear or desire to avoid him and said,
I came to this place with this youth to hide the most precious part of our plunder that the emperor might not come to know of it.
This, she said, by way of an excuse, and he, pretending to be convinced, let it pass,
although he saw that the belt which held theodosius' drawers over his private parts was undone,
for he was so overpowered by his love for the creature that he preferred not to believe
his own eyes.
However, Antoninas the Vachery went from bad to worse until it reached a shameful pitch.
All who beheld that were silent except one slave woman named Macedonia, who, when Belsarius
was that Syracuse, after the conquest of Sicily, first made her master swear the most solemn oaths
that he would never betray her to his mistress, never betray her to her mistress, and then told
him the whole story, bringing as her witnesses two boys who attended Antonina's bedchamber.
When Belisarius heard this, he told some of his guards to make away with Theodosius,
but the latter, being warned in time, led to Euthesius, for the greater part of Belisarius's
followers influenced by natural weakness of his character, were at more pains to please his wife
than to show their devotion to him. And this was why they disclosed to her the orders which
they received concerning Theodosius. When Constantine saw Belisarius's sorrow at what had
For my own part, I would have killed the woman rather than the youth.
This having been reported to Antonina, she could see the secret hatred for him until she
could make him feel the weight of her resentment for she was like a scorpion and knew how to
hide her venom.
Not long afterwards, either by enchantments or by caresses, she persuaded her husband that
the accusation brought upon her was false whereupon, without any hesitation, he sent
forth theodosius and promised to deliver up his wife Macedonia and the boys, which he
afterwards did.
It is said that she first cut out their tongues and then ordered them to be hewned in pieces
into the sacs and thrown into the sea.
In this bloody deed, she was assisted by one of her slaves named Eugenius, who had been
one of those who perpetrated the outrage of Silverius.
Shortly afterward, Belisarius was persuaded by his wife to kill Constantine.
What I've already recounted about Prisiddarius and his daggers belongs to
this period. Belisarius would have let him go but Antonina
would not rest until she had exacted vengeance for the words which I had
just repeated. The murder stirred up a great hatred against
Belisarius and the part of the emperor and the chief nobles of the emperor.
How long is, how long is, okay, it's almost over,
it's just three, four paragraphs.
So it says, such was the course of events.
Meanwhile, theodosius refused to return to Italy.
where Bilisarius and Antonina were then staying until
Photius was sent out of his way for Photius was naturally disposed to show his spite against anyone who supplanted him in another script graces
And he was quite right in feeling jealous of the odosius because he himself although Antonina's son was quite neglected
Whereas the other was exceedingly powerful and had taken treasure amounted to a hundred centenars of gold about
$400,000 from the treasure houses of the two cities of Carthage and Ravenna
since he had obtained sole and absolute control of the management of them.
When Antonina heard this determination of the Eidosias, she never ceased to lay traps for her son
and to concoct unnatural plots against him, until she made him see that he must leave
her and retire to Byzantium, for he could no longer endure the designs against his life.
At the time, she made the Eidosias's return to Italy, where she enjoyed the full,
the society of her lover, thanks to the easy, good nature of her husband.
Later on she returned to Byzantium and company with both of them. It was there that Theodosius
became alarmed lest their intimacy should become known, and was greatly embarrassed,
not knowing what to do. That it could remain undetected to the end he felt was impossible,
for he saw that the woman was no longer able to conceal her passion and indulge it in secret,
but was an open and avowed adulteress, and did not blush to be called so.
For this reason he returned to Ephesius, and having submitted to the Trettonshire,
At this Antonina entirely lost her reason, showed her distress by putting on mourning
and her general behavior enrolment about the house, wailing and lamenting, even the presence
of her husband, the good friend she had lost, so faithful, so pleasant, so tender a companion,
so prompt in action. At last she even won over her husband to begin to utter the same lamentations.
The poor fool kept calling for the return of his well-beloved theodosius and afterward.
went to the emperor and besought him and the emperors, till he prevailed upon them,
to send for the Odossias as a man whose services would always have been and always would be
indispensable to the household. The Odossias however refers to obey, declaring that it was
his fixed determination to remain in the cloister and embrace the monastic life,
but this language was by no means sincere, or was his intention as soon as Belisarius left
the country to rejoin Antonina by stealth and Byzantium, as in fact he did. So there you go,
It's a full of intrigue. She definitely sound like a cheat, you know
That was her best. That was the Empress's best friend. We'll get to the Empress later. The Empress is just as bad, right? So
When this story it's kind of like, you know, it's a little bit to me
It seems a little bit steam addiction stream addiction can make your life unmanageable real talk. Well random guy. Why are you?
Giving me your two cents
Okay, random guy become a member and I'll take your opinion more seriously
Until then it's like why are you like telling me negative things stop it
Okay, be careful with the stay working for them the devilish ones, right? Okay. Yeah, I know it seems like they're a little bit
You know it's kind of big a little bit evil back then what is it you it gets a lot worse. I mean she starts like you know, no
I'm unaliving a lot of people stuff, and uh, but but it's kind of interesting. I'll get random guys crying
Yeah, so let's see
How'd everyone like this story? Yeah, hold on
Easy has no clue what I'm saying. Did you understand what I was the book was about or the stories about so I mean it's confusing with the names
I was listening. Yeah, she cheated on the nigga that she convinced them that she was it and then
All that bullshit
I ain't want to handle that. She's a cheater. Oh
Yeah, and she also fell in love with her adopted son, I think
So and when someone has blast for me that blast for me
That blasphemy, I don't know if they're even,
I guess they're working on it.
That was just the word that popped into my head.
Blasphemy, I think it would be more like, you know,
taboo or incest or something like that,
but it became very part of it.
It's from a book called The Secret History by Procopius.
It's about the emperor's, Theodora emperor,
emperor of the Sinian.
It's like the secret history.
Told by one of like I think a philosopher of the day like a famous philosopher, but I
May I think he was you must have been intimate
Okay, well, so let me see my tablet is like kind of disappointing me say a little bit
Start
charging
It's not broken already. I just got this fucking thing. Oh, here it goes. I just broke the charger
You saying that yeah, I just I just went to go put a charger in earlier and it snapped right when I plugged it in
I'm like what? Oh
Yeah, I didn't have a sense of your audience and ADHD so reading off 15 minute paragraphs may not be the best idea
Exposed. Okay. Well, okay. So I used to be a teacher reading class even if you weren't a good reader
You can get main themes to written passages. Well, that's true. But that's why
you know, they have the Cliff's Notes, right?
There's also some websites, I think it's called Spark Notes,
and it has like a bunch of, like even Russian novels,
Russian novels are notoriously complicated
and impossible to understand,
but it breaks it down like really, really well,
and it's really interesting,
because they're brilliant authors of them,
but they're just a little bit complicated
to like read translated on their own,
but there's some interesting stories.
There's one called by Fyodor Diodosky,
Called the called devils. It's really interesting. You can check that one out
These novels from other countries how better are they than Americans?
Well, I mean America has some great American novels, but I mean the Russian novels are
Like, for example, have you heard of Ulysses?
Have you heard of the book Ulysses, right?
Have you heard of that book?
No, no.
It's by James Joyce.
It's kind of like a modern day version of the Odyssey.
But it's very, very, very, it'll take a long time
to understand.
Have you guys, are you familiar with Ulysses, anybody?
It's just written in a very, like.
When I read, I read fantasy, fantasy and comic books.
Yeah, I mean it's like it is very it's just complicated
I mean it's like you know some of them are very hard to read, but they're beautiful stories
But they're just like wow they are detailed you've read it. How was it man? Was it was it a tough read?
Yeah, man to read it Amanda Areson and it's it's a famous novel
You can also watch the little summaries of like novels on you read in high school. It was a high school
Wow, it's in high school. I read I read some complicated novels
I mean some of them are very complicated, but it's like I would you know and I was a good reader English was my top subject
But it's still they were
You know, it's English is remembering details or deeply names. I'm not great at names. I'm not good at numbers either. Like
Yo, if I meet your public, we I'll make you a
Like other than psyche, I'll give you a nickname
Especially if your name is some some funny name. I'm like, yeah
Hey, your name is Christine. I'm like, yo Steve
Sec he is a nickname though. Hey Sebastian. No, I did not receive anything. I don't have a bank of America
I don't I have a different bank. Okay, so it says the alien Odyssey were your favorites. Yeah, I love though
I love the Odyssey in the Iliad. Yeah, they the Odyssey's by Homer is like, you know, supposedly the world's first novel and
You know, it's like kind of like the school you know what schools do schools hoodwink people because they want to simply leave that Greek mythology and
Again, they on the the Odyssey all these things were just like we're written ancient times like you know
Yeah, right. I mean, it's just like they're written probably more recently and stuff and presented as
Ancient things, but if you look at like some of the schools, right? So when did where was school actually created?
School I believe you know as clean this first rules were in Greece and they were like but they would they basically though
But the big the philosophers would take on students and so they would be like, you know
Alexander the great like I think was tutored by Socrates and that right guys
And then, you know, so these are, but this is a kind of mythology because Homer is, they'll say they don't know if Homer was a male or a man or a woman, and they don't know if Homer existed at all.
It was an oral tradition at first, and so when they say oral tradition, yeah, it's been told over years, but who's to say that it's making it up at the time, and they're saying it was passed on.
You don't know, and also in oral traditions.
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to get. Like, where was the reaction created? How far is the...
School I think I think the education was started it probably in in Greece, you know
And that was where the first schools were but there are also these mystery schools in Egypt as well
But but Egypt was very attached to Greece, you know, because I was the end of the great to the conquest there
And so so there was like a lot of similar similarity between the gods and you know
There's equivalence to the Egyptian gods to the Greek gods. Okay
I'm off today. That's good. Okay. Yeah. Oh, that's awesome. You have two advanced degrees reading is what so
Reading so what I do. Yeah, it reads what you do
Drainings when I say this should drink my battery
It's fast five percent. I had a great song since I keep thinking okay the first up next up hit the link in the top
Later, thank you
Okay
Okay, Agamemnon, yeah, I've actually been to Greece.
I've seen the mask of Agamemnon.
So let me see, okay, so 1%, so I need to plug it back in.
Okay, ah!
Let me turn off again, shit.
Okay.
Okay, so,
I was, this is a low power charger, shit.
Well, that's not good.
Okay.
So,
I'll read it. I'll try to read a Norse mythology if it doesn't tablet doesn't die
It says that it there's a book. This is my I have this is not like a long. They're very short. They're fine
See, I've read one before but I very
Okay, so this is called this is called Zeus grants stupid wishes, okay
And they have a Norse mythology section
Norse, okay, so
This is holy shit my friends this meet those we are coming up on right now is a cosmological equivalent of French kissing a battle axe
These myths are rude, crude, and probably radioactive, they play music too loud and draw disapprovingly
looks from the elderly.
They will wake up your mother in the middle of the night by driving a Humvee through the
armoire.
Seriously, any mythology in which the principal characters are a SUICIDAL, pirate wizard, and
what essentially amounts to a beard with a hammer sticking out of it is a mythology
for me and for you two once the Norse get through with you.
So it says, you might may already know that the way the Greeks thought the world got made and also the Romans because the Romans are goddamn copycaters
And maybe you have listened to some scientists or creation scientists, and you know one or two other ways
Listen, I want you to forget everything you know about creation myths because the myth this myth is going to blow your dick off
from pure wonderment and if you have not got a dick
It's going to sew one on and immediately blow it off want to know why because it's North mythology time shit
Yeah, so to start out the world is already pretty badass. It's just two things
One is see a pure all-devouring fire called must bell
Guarded by a dude named cert who is just waiting to ride out and murder all the gods and then set the world on fire
By comparison the other half of the world is pretty lame. It's just a bunch of ice called nipalime
But the best part is that
Between moosebell and nipolime, there's a big-ass trench called genugugugup,
which is empirically proven to be the number one funniest thing to say.
Go ahead and say it. I'll wait. So genugugup is where the shit starts to get real,
because the cold from nipolime bumps up against the heat from moosebell.
It caused a bunch of vapor to condense in genugugup to create a frost giant in genugugup,
Actually, Ymir is more of an ogre than a giant, and he's more of a wuss than an ogre.
Because what is the first thing this guy does?
He goes to sleep right there in Ganungagap, sweating and sleeping like a motherfucker.
He sweats so hard that a man and a woman throw out of his armpit, and then he sweats even
harder, causing his legs to fuck each other and have a baby.
So then this cow shows up and starts shooting milk everywhere, and Ymir drinks all of it,
because there's pretty much no one else to drink it, other than his leg baby and the
Then the cow gets bored and starts licking ice, and all the licking melts away enough
ice to form the shape of a dude, or maybe it's just the same dude who appeared in Yamir's
armpit.
Yamir has mastered the fine art of being a neglectful father.
Anyway, the guy's name is Bohr.
He marries Bess Bislah, the daughter of some giant.
Maybe the daughter of Yamir, who knows.
Bohr is quite a catch because he is the only man in existence.
Really, the only one, anyone gives a shit about is Odin, he's the ruler of all things essentially and he gets his brothers to help him kill Ymir, who's probably still asleep.
and has definitely not done anything to deserve being murdered.
But Odin thinks, seems to think he has become too evil,
which perhaps means that he was snoring really loud.
Whatever the reason they kill you, Myr.
Nice patricide, Odin.
What are you gonna do next?
Further desecrate your grandfather's body
by tearing him apart and using his limbs
as decoration for a universe you and your brothers are making?
Yes, that is exactly what Odin and his brothers do.
I mean, you gotta give them credit.
They pretty much use every part of the dude.
Like, not only do they make
his blood into lakes and oceans and bones into mountains, skin into earth, his teeth into tiny rocks,
but they use his skull to make the sky, which is such a dumb idea that
they have to get some cheap slave labor to make it work, so they go over to Ymir's corpse,
which is crawling with maggots at this point, and they're like, hey maggots, want to be a sentient
humanoid species? And the maggots are like, do we? So they turn into dwarves and Odin's like,
We wanted to make it into the sky but skulls are really not meant for that.
We'll even name the guys who do it north south east and west.
It'll be awesome and the dwarves are like okay fine.
But listen guys, just because they already have used Ymir's skull and skin and bones and teeth
and blood does not mean they have finished the filing of his corpse because the next thing they
do is they chuck his brains into the air and they become clouds.
Do you think that clouds were beautifully fluffy collections of water vapor?
And then they make the stars out of all the sparks coming out of moosebell and give all the land along the coast of the giants
I guess to say
Sorry for murdering amir and building the world out of his corpse
But the giants are still pissed and odin is like i need a fort to protect myself from all these giants
What will i build it out of oh?
I know eyebrows and then he before he builds becomes a safe haven for all the humans called midgard
And they drag emir's corpse over ganungagap and odin makes a place called asgard
and surprisingly a few of Ymir's body parts,
using surprisingly a few of Ymir's body parts.
And he lives there with his wife Frigga
and is startlingly faithful to her
and fathers all the other gods who are called the Yisir.
So the moral of the story is that
we need to invest space travel with quickness
because all of Ymir's body parts
are about to get real ripe real fast.
Yeah, you like that one?
That was a good one.
I say, teach it as an adjunct?
Yeah, I would like to go over some of this stuff
and like, you know, different.
I was really into reading, actually fairy tales,
but I was like reading them in high school,
like analyzing like the psychological part.
I even have like a bunch of round here,
like books of all about the psychology of the fairy tale
and stuff like that, because they are, you know, archetypal.
So.
Yeah, so Mickey D's is hiring. Well, why would I want to work there? I mean, did you pay 20 bucks an hour?
Which is more than I make now, but you know
I'm gonna have to leave the house. I don't really like McDonald's food
It's okay
Hi guys
Okay, guys. We're doing good. You wait. Okay, so you want you want another one? I'll do another Norse one if you liked it
Okay, this one called door got hammered
Says when Odin finally gets done making the world and settles down to get busy with his wife Frigga
The first radical dude to get born is named Thor. Thor is pretty much the baddest motherfucker
You will ever lay eyes on and in fact if you ever laid eyes on him
He would probably walk up to you and destroy your eyes with his hammer
Thor's hammer is called Mjolnir, and it was made like so.
So Loki, the god of being a needless prick all the time,
sneaks up on Thor's wife, siff one day,
and shaves off all her hair, like he's one of the guys
on Jackass or something.
And Thor really loves hair, I guess,
so he gets super angry and chases down Loki,
and he's like, hey!
How about I cut off all of your face the loki's like but I need my face for making infuriating remarks with or smirks with
And Thor's like well, how about I just break every bone in your body and loki's like no
I need those two is it how about I instead I have the dwarves make your wife some new hair
It'll be made of gold. It will grow like normal hair and Thor's like awesome
So Loki goes to the dwarves and it's like guys
I sort of promised Thor that you would make his wife the ultimate to pay
and the dwarves are like sure no problem do you want us to make it out of gold or double gold
because we really fucking like gold because we're dwarves
And hey, by the way, I'm sorry for being a racist against doors, but that is how the doors are, okay?
Some of my best friends are dwarves. Anyway, Loki is like regular gold is fine, and the dwarves are like, okay, okay?
Well, how about we also make you a boat called Skibb-a-Denir,
which you can fit all your friends and all your treasure and always have wind in a sail and can be folded up and put in
your pocket with not unused. And how about we also make Odin a spear, scratch that in unstoppable spear and
Loki is like damn all we ever did for you guys was make you hold up this guy forever
So Loki brings all the sweet loot back to the gods and then he gets this great idea
Which is to bet the doors that they can't make three even more better treasures for free
But he doesn't have much cash on him
So instead he just bets them his head and these dwarves named rock and it take the deal because it's not like they
Have to bet anything themselves and they go to the forge
and Brock pulls out his big-ass boar skin and he's like, okay, E.T. is completely crucial,
that you crank the bellows constantly, so E.T. starts doing it pretty soon, a big-ass fly lands
on the hand and stings the shit out of it, but E.T. doesn't care, he's going crazy with that bellows,
so Brock makes what he's trying to make, he brings it to Loki, and he's like, okay, so we all love
boars, right, but you know what would make a boar even better? Gold, gold makes everything better,
And I covered this fucking bore in gold. Okay. Look guys. I'm just telling the story
It's not fair to apply our modern conception of racism to a bygone past
Okay, I forget what the term for it is but don't do it anyway the filthy dwarves still need to make two more things
So Brock decides to cut off the middleman and just put some gold directly on the forge
And he's like hey each you remember what you do with the bore just do exactly that but
Because it is totally crucial. So ET starts working the bellows and lo and behold the same fucking fly shows up and bites them on his neck
But ET just tuffs it out and it keeps on pumping and Brock finishes the thing he's making and brings it to Loki
So take out this ring I made I call it Rappner
But the thing is this is just one gold ring. Do you think that is enough gold?
I don't think that it's enough gold
So for what I made it to do is every ninth night it shits out eight identical rings that we so many rings
I can melt them down for their gold and then use them to make more rings and then drop more out more rings
I can create an infinite gold. This is the dream of every dwarf because we love gold so much
Do you know we invented rings so we could have sex with gold? Okay, okay, okay?
Hold on guys. Do you have any dwarf friends?
Maybe you could just have them not read this myth if they have read this far
It is already too late. We pretty much done with the gold part and you have lost a friend. Anyway
Then Brock puts a big ass chunk of iron on the forge and E.T. starts pumping the bellows and then the same fucking fly comes back and bites his eyelids, his eyelids, but E.T. is just pumping until blooded from the gaping wounds from this fly has inflicted trickles down into his eye and he takes one hand up the bellows so wipe away the blood and the bellow stops and everything is ruined.
It was supposed to be a hammer called Mjolnir, but now it is a hammer called Mjolnir with a kind of short handle.
and Brock is like dang maybe I won't get Loki's head after all and so he bundles up the shit and
takes it to Asgard because quitting us for pussies and in Asgard all the gods are like holy
damn you made a ring that shits out more rings and you do not have to be adored to appreciate
infinite gold oh the board the board is pretty nice too I can use more gold maybe and then
doors like guys this hammer is so sweet it hits anything I throw it at and then it always comes
But that doesn't keep it from never missing guys. You realize how many frost giants we can kill with that
This is the best Norse Christmas ever and Brock is like looks like I won the bet Loki
I'm going to dip your head in gold and then probably fuck it. That's what I do because I'm a dwarf
Look, I lie when I said the gold part was over if you had your dwarf friend
Just keep reading because you have thought the damage was done and I'm really sorry man
But you need taller friends
So Loki starts running as fast as he can and door gets gets the hammer that could hit anything a hundred percent of the time
and he just kind of knocks Loki out and brings them back and Loki's like,
wait, I promised you my head, but I never promised you the neck that it rests on.
So you can't cut it up. Ha! So Brock just shows Loki's mouth shut instead,
which is probably the best thing for everybody.
So what do we learn today? Is that dwarves give the best birthday gifts.
So if you should try to make up with your dwarf friend, no matter how short they are,
or how bad they smell, or how much they keep eyeing your gold earrings and licking their lips,
but that's not the last wacky plan that gods came up with to avoid paying for shit.
There we go. I hope you liked like that my uh
You like gold yeah, I like I like I'm platinum better like gold. I thought I think that's kind of like brown
I don't know people seem to love it. Is it rare? I don't know if it's even rare
Being poor at the worst, you know
Be on the street and be homeless as a president not having a bathroom shower kitchen fridge and privacy
That's the worst for being in prison
Well in prison all those things are taken care of you have the bathrooms you have the showers you have the kitchen you have the fridge
You have some privacy relatively, but I guess not that much show your butthole and stuff
Yeah
Yeah, so maybe you privacy you stand for prison as for the street there are
Bathrooms, I mean there are on this, you know, there's I know it's not very good. I
Rather have people in hotel, you know, they put they put them all a lot of people in the Roosevelt
They took all the tents cities down that were here. It was good stuff. You liked it like five them, too. Yeah
Got a little bit of you when you're poor with no money because money ain't everything no money's not everything
You can't take money with you money is actually just a thing. It's just something it's something is it maybe it can be
converted into energy in a certain way, but it's basically fiat currency unless it's like, you know, gold or silver
It's not really
You know and we can't just trade shells or gold and silver, you know, it's like so
You've been a poor to you, but definitely like having money better, right? Well, you know, I've been I've been blessed enough to
So always, you know, I would never have to be homeless and I've you know, I've always been very fortunate in that way
But it's so bit money or no money to take people that money doesn't buy happiness
There are billionaires that are just miserable people there are
Almost people that are living in bliss, you know, and so it's like
This depends, you know, it's really about how you look at life and what you're also looking for in life
some people like like the
lifestyle where you're out fishing and and you know catching your dinner and doing a little beach
Grill and sleeping in a tent under the stars and
You know swimming in the ocean in the morning to get you know, it's like it's almost sounds that sounds pretty nice to me
It sounds like a vacation, you know, but
I think some people pay, people here pay money to like go to the, these huts in Thailand,
these little huts, right?
And like, you know, they're not very expensive.
And you know, we enjoy it as long as, as long as the setting is beautiful, it's just like
when it's a concrete jungle, when it's like, you know, there's like people fighting over
stuff.
And I don't know.
And also, I think we treat some illegal people better than American citizens, which I don't
Yeah, well, let's see a random guy look at how the but how life can change and that reminds me of a quote
Every saint has a past and every sinner has a future
Think about that
You're suing this wreck. Oh, yeah
So, random guy, we probably have more in common than anything, but maybe, I don't know, we'll talk about it some day.
A thing that keeps us from being homeless, what is the thing? It's the fear of it, right? It's like, or else it's the...
It's we're blessed, but we there's a rifle for years as trust manager for a bank
There's an old woman. She managed that a few million dollars that insist on leaving it on the streets. No living on the streets
Yeah, I've heard about I've heard about that
I've heard there was some guy like a guy that was found like dead a homeless guy
And he had like three million dollars in a shopping cart or something like that, you know, and he was just
Some people enjoy that or some people, you know, there's mental illness to some people
This is too much for some people, right?
Tell her many times you could get her apartment managing all bills. You wouldn't have it
Sometimes we go through bad patches and tough times financially immensely or physically with an injury part of life
Got to take it one day at a time one at a time, right?
And it's also we have to help each other, right?
It's like we have to make sure like, you know, we're watching out for fellow citizens and like there's so many other problems in the world are just from
a lot of it's from
ostracizing people from just like you know bullying from hate you know like
people sometimes snap we also the Joker what happens when the Joker right but
you know if you have tough times sometimes there's angels that help you
sometimes it's like part of your part of the you know things you come up for time
asking for a few bucks and disappear oh so you're the trust yeah interesting you
know but it's like you know also a lot of the Tibetan llamas like the early
Yeah, maybe mentally ill or just we're just enjoyed that maybe she's an angel in disguise. You never know, right?
but uh
Yeah, you never know, right? It is wild
But I think that you know
There's enough people think that oh the population is going there's too many people here eight billion or six billion people eight billion people
Whatever. Yeah, a lot of people
There's plenty of room still see how much of America is just like an empty land
You know, it's just like how much of the world is an empty land is like, you know, tons like
Maybe it's a lot of its own or not to be developed
But also we can also build up like we can build skyscrapers
We also can build economically like you know the Saudi Arabia
I think they have this wall and it's like you can like live inside the wall and like you can like it has like little like
Transportation to go everywhere has like, you know, it's only inside garden and stuff in gardens and it's like all
You know eco solar power and
It's kind of like a utopia kind of stuff, but it kind of sounds a little bit like a prison. Yeah
I know I was gonna say prison, right? It's like it's a both, but it's nice though
It's like and so it's like, you know, we do kind of you can look at earth as a prison in a certain way, right?
Eco prison
Well, how about tiny homes? How about that? I mean, I would even fit inside a tiny home, right?
I mean a tiny home as it can be like a
Munchkins would live in a tiny but people having you know people saw me or living these tiny homes
I did like a dog house for a human. I really you also order a house on Amazon for like I think 10 grand
And they'll bring you a house. You just put on some land. Nobody can find a lady at all. Wow
But prison is like you know some some people like prison because it's like for some men it's like camp for me
It would be kind of fun because I'd just be like I'd probably have a finally have a boyfriend. I'd uh, you know
Just like keep myself to you know have like a little kitchen job and
Maybe lots of sex that would make it all worth it. But a lot of guys wouldn't like that
Van life. Yeah, same with van life. Yeah, we have this guy on the show. His name is the elf guy
I was in there with dark dark elf. I'm not sure. It's the same dark elf or something
It's a little yeah, it's a little it's a little crowded though your privacy
That's priceless. Yeah, but like who your privacy doesn't mean anything if it's not respected
And so it's like what happened in like the this thing called the Stasi
That was introduced the East German secret police and what happened was they started like
having like everyone spy on each other, you know for the for the state and like then all of a sudden like
They went from like the neighbor spying on each other on each other
See like the families would have been to bring in the people and then the fan the fan
Then they turn people in so they'd bring more people in and so families which are telling each other
So it was like mothers were telling their kids kids with other parents
It was just like a mess and then like pretty much almost everyone was locked up and then they're like, okay
Well, we need to rethink this but yeah, they would uh
They would just say be spying like crazy, right?
Yeah
Well
Yeah, but the good thing is that our court system is set up for the privacy laws
And so it's like, you know, you can like take a legal surveillance is fine. You just can't it's not admissible in any court
Think about how would you like to have your you know, if you have a wife or house that I would like to have them
Then recorded like through the window the high-powered, you know, telescope or whatever like some nearby hotel like
My own bath tub shower fridge and bedroom is worth it. Yeah. Yeah, I know it is it is I'm very lucky
Especially especially Los Angeles is very expensive. Hell no what?
I thought once you had to move, yeah
Yeah, well now it's getting like, you know brick in it. Yeah little it's people. It's getting very
Invasive like people wanting to spy on each other people are you know, and it's like I know it's for like whatever
But it's like what I know will happen. Oh, you know
Slowly slowly
It'll turn into East Germany again
Probably be a wall bills until people just have had had enough of it and
Stand up for themselves and their rights, right?
People recording you and family held not well right, but they think about like the phones phones can be hacked
The there's cameras and these things are the cameras can all be hacked
They're you know, the information is pretty much public, but now it's like there's like a big you know, it's easier to
Go places that you're easier to communicate. I mean a lot of things are easier
do
It's all in say, I don't know. It's just it's pretty dangerous, right?
I mean privacy with having your apartment instead of in the street or shelter with prison or mental health was stranger. Yeah
Yeah, unless you're nice unless you're you're in a you're in a you know solitary confinement. That's privacy, right?
Plenty of privacy there
See, there's such a thing as too much privacy, too.
There's also such a thing as being trapped in your own home
as like, our home's going to be a prison.
We're going to put ourselves in gated communities.
It's like, we're just like, we keep everyone out, right?
But that's what prisons do the same thing.
They have gates, right?
That's all.
So it's the very rich and the very poor
both have a gated community, right?
A prison or a, anyway.
Let's see.
This, this sounds like a funny book. Let me see. I think some, probably guys can, says,
I always hated being an adult. I resented the fact of being so caught up in growing up
stuff, like forgetting to pay my bills, finding stocks that match and lying about why I was late
for work, that I lost sight of everything, that ever made me happy as a child. I gave up on popping
wheelies, I stopped ding dong ditching, and I don't even think spitballs or really loud farts
were as funny as they used to be. I haven't drawn a dick on something in years.
And I couldn't even remember the last time I threw a party at my parents' house when they weren't home, or when I had sex with a 16-year-old girl in the backseat of my mom's car.
But by my 40th birthday, I was completely broken and just a shell of that fry boy who left the loudest parts in the fifth grade.
Shortly after I graduated college, I needed to find a fucking job and move the hell out so I could start paying my own goddamn bills already.
At least that's what my parents were telling me.
My parents didn't understand was that I was a psychology major.
get good jobs or move out of their parents' house with a shitty college major and not enough charm
or good looks to enter the lucrative world of pharmaceutical sales like my mom and dad wanted
me to. It looks like I was destined to smoke pot all day and live with my parents forever.
With a little luck and a fuckload of white privilege, my life is finally on the right track.
I healed the damaged relationship with my father, even though he could be a real dick sometimes.
I was also awakened to my inner child.
Now I'm the same fun-loving, happy-go-lucky kid who used to masturbate five times a day
and play with matches.
I have dental insurance, an amicable divorce, and two kids who aren't in therapy yet.
I'm even back to drawing dicks on people's stuff at work again.
My inspirational story of faith help and redemption will change your life forever.
If you don't believe it, my third cousin from Jersey didn't read it and he's still on heroin.
My neighbor didn't read it either and he's a nosy dick who can't ever mind his own fucking
business.
My nana and pop didn't read it.
Now they're both dead.
If you don't want to end up dead like my nana and pop, you need to read this book.
You like it?
Hi guys.
Okay.
Sometimes it takes losing everything to begin to appreciate anything, at least that's what happened to me.
By the time I was 35 years old, everything good in my life was gone. I had lost my home, my kids, my wife, and my job.
I lost it all. It was just another homeless vagrant. I was no different from Sylvester Stallone and the other 11 famous people you wouldn't believe were homeless
that I read about on my phone during my daughter's boring dance recital last month.
Where I would get my next meal, where I would shower again, or even where I would take a decent shit without being arrested or freaking anyone out.
It was awful. I would go days without brushing my teeth and sometimes I'd even go for weeks without flossing.
I couldn't watch The Walking Dead anymore. I even missed the final episode of Breaking Bad.
With no access to my favorite television shows, being homeless was the hardest thing I had to face in my whole entire life.
I would not wish such a fate on my worst enemy, not even my fat fuck of a boss, who was constantly
busting my balls about being late to work all the time. The whole time I was homeless,
I kept looking for salvation, but all I ever found was the bottom of a natural ice can,
the worst kind of beer known to man, the kind of beer only drank by poor people in college kids.
I was on a crash course told stuff to structure them ruin, and also cheap beer. It was only by
the grace of God, but in the help of a few kind souls that I was able to rise like a phoenix out
discover true happiness and start getting drunk on delicious craft beer again. My life as a
homeless person taught me a lot of valuable lessons. It taught me way more about living my best life,
the power of positive thinking, energy gifts, self-love, courage, affirmation, eye statements,
or any other that stupid bullshit and all those self-help books that my mom buys for Christmas
Yeah, it defined my character, it fostered my resilience, it even taught me how to love
myself again.
Now I'm back to loving myself three or four times a day, just like I did when I was back
in middle school.
Well, yes, I got a bit ahead of myself.
Before I go any further, let me tell you everything that happened to me on this extraordinary
journey that led to self-discovery and spiritual enlightenment.
I will share with you the entire story of my tragic fall and epic rise, all the way to
the catharsis that helped reset my narcissistic mindset so that I can exist on a higher plane
of consciousness than the rest of you.
You need to hear my backstory. I need to tell you about how I came face-to-face with vile and despicable foes such as bosses, co-workers, wives, children, teachers, pets, parents, family, friends, and how their constant barrage of bullshit and nagging led me down a path of self-destruction and ruin.
This is what we writers like to call a backstory. At least, I think it's called a backstory. It might actually be called an opening or maybe an introduction, but I'm pretty sure it's backstory.
Braveheart, Alien, Predator, and even all those Jason and Freddie movies, they all have great backstories.
Let's examine the backstory of Braveheart for the minute.
Braveheart managed to win five Oscars, even though Mel Gibson hates Jews.
That's how good it was. In this movie, Mel Gibson paints his face and kills everyone.
Not a bad plot for a movie, but not exactly Oscar worthy either.
Now, add a backstory where the entire family gets killed by the bad guys, now we're talking five Oscars.
Schwarzenegger did a similar movie called Commando.
In this movie, Arnold was just a simple,
retired commando living in the middle of the desert
when suddenly the bad guys busted and kidnapped his daughter,
which obviously forces them to paint his face
and kill everyone.
There's a fantastic movie called Robocop,
which has a great backstory as well.
In this movie, a police officer gets shot
and turned into a robot cop who winds up,
obviously winds up killing everyone as well.
Just to be clear, as much as I love movies
about people who paint their faces or get turned into robots,
and wind up killing everyone. This is not what happened to me. I was just simply citing those
examples of good backstories because I have a pretty amazing backstory as well. It's probably
not as good as getting turned into a robot or being a secret commando and killing everyone,
but it's still a pretty good one. You see, I was once an optimistic young man who had a very
promising future. I absolutely loved life and treasured every moment. I would spend every day
And frolic in the autumn leaves are simply first in the song, but then something happened.
I stopped being me. I stopped being that fun-loving, happy-go-lucky kid who masturbated five times a day and played with matches.
I didn't play with my G.I. Joe's or Transformers anymore. I gave up popping wheelies and vandalizing stuff.
No more spitballs or really loud farts, which were hilarious as they used to be.
I stopped getting stoned before school and it couldn't tell you the loud time I threw a party at my parents' house
when they weren't home or when I had sex with a 16-year-old girl in the backseat of my mom's car.
Somewhere along the way, I lost sight of everything that made me happy as a child
I was too wrapped up in the hustle and bustle of everyday grown-up stuff like finding socks that match taking showers getting dressed
Looking for car keys looking for my wallet trying to get in my house after I locked myself out paying
Overdrafties forgetting about my dirty dishes and during late notices not taking the garbage out spanking the shit out of my kids complaining about stuff
Coming up with about why I was late to work because of being a real grown-up had become a such a burden that life had lost its bluster
joy and innocence of my youth that was dead. I'll be honest, I never knew that being an adult
would be such hard work. I always figured my whole life would be just ball into place. I would
have the kind of guy who would look like a male model and wore khaki pants just like all those
docker's commercials with all those handsome guys wearing khaki pants. I assumed that I would have
six pack abs, a million dollars, and a smoking hot wife with really huge fake tits that we would
make out all the time in public and do really trendy parenting stuff like pay attention to our kids.
Never in our wildest dreams did I think I would grow up
to become a homeless guy drinking natty ice
out of a brown paper bag.
But there I was, by my 40th birthday,
I was nothing more than a shell of that spry and gallant young man
and his whole life had in front of him
and left the loudest parts of fifth grade.
Here's how it all happened.
Oh, how long is this story?
Okay, that's only a few more minutes.
You like it?
Bunny?
Okay.
Where is everybody here?
So, it says, my story begins in the spring of 2001 on the campus of the U.S. News 135th
Desk Liberal Arts College in the entire United States of America.
You probably never heard of it.
I can assure you it's a very prestigious school.
In fact, it's better than 134 other colleges in that specific category, including that
particular rating.
This school is so elite that it only accepts 72% of its applicants. Now, not that I'm bragging, but in 1997 it happened to be one of those
applicants. I know statistics may seem a little tight and boring.
You're probably wondering where I was going to do with all this,
but the figure are much needed an element in my story because they provide the necessary
empirical data to support my mom's undying belief that I was indeed a very special boy. So on a faithful day,
In spring in 2001, in the quaint little college town nestled in the foothills of Pennsylvania,
I was about to graduate college and embark on my journey into manhood and greatness.
Now to some skeptics, they might argue that college degree doesn't hold as much value as it
used to. Sure, I did borrow $65,000 to take a useless major that will eventually not get me
a good job from a mediocre college that no one has ever heard of. And sure, I'll never be able
to pay back those loans and my credit wouldn't someday be ruined because of it. And that doesn't
The graduation was a fine and wonderful ceremony. It was well-known keynote speaker
who I'm sure had some very profound words. I don't remember what they were but I'm sure
speech was very good. The ceremony itself was wonderful too. It has pumped in a lot of circumstances
and it even had a blistery hot sun that was beating down on me for hours upon hours and every
single last thing got called even the names of the people who had the shitty majors like philosophy
Graduations are pure torture. I'd rather have someone put cigarette out of my eyelids while I
sodomize me with a cactus than go to graduation ceremony. Now even worse, I'd rather go to my
third cousin's gender reveal party. Newsflash Jessica, you're not the first person to have a
baby. No one gives a shit about what you're having.
Anyway, the castles were churned, my graduation finally ended.
It was somewhere between holding in a fart and looking at my watch because that was
what I would usually do with this sort of thing.
That's when something wonderful and extraordinary happened out of nowhere.
The whole entire audience stood up and erupted with applause.
It was a standing ovation.
I couldn't believe it.
I puffed my chest out proudly because everyone loved me.
It was the proudest moment of my life.
I was not expecting that sort of praise and adulation.
didn't realize that people were such big fans of psychology majors. I bet Jesus Christ himself
never had a standing ovation and he performed miracles. I'll be honest based on my major
GPA drinking drug use, the assortment of disorderly conduct, my cheating, worth the ethic. Overall
this position I probably deserved the opposite of standing ovation. I probably deserved a room full
of silent parts. I had no job and nowhere to live. I was in debt up to my ears. I was drunk all the
One of my dad's buddies was a degenerate gambler.
He lived that way for years, and no one ever
gave him a standing ovation.
But then again, he didn't graduate from college either.
It was truly the proudest day of my life.
Yeah, who is that Trevor?
Okay, is that somebody?
Used to be settlements that are in cities
and out of gated communities, forts, okay.
About staying safe from them, stay from others, right?
Yeah, stay from other people, right?
Keeping the criminals out and keeping ourselves in
Well, it's like, you know anybody that wishes us harm
So I think I'm gonna have my
Okay
This this this book is called am I the asshole a memoir so that was that book. Do you like that book?
Okay, let me see let me see if they have the story
This is have a book about
Okay
This is a book about fairy tales and like the unconscious and stuff like that. It's called shadow and evil and fairy tales
It's a by Carl Jung one of his best students. Okay
It is called the Two Travelers as a story.
It says, the Two Travelers says, mountain and valley do not meet, but human beings sometimes
do both good and bad.
So it happens that a tailor and a shoemaker met in their wanderings.
The tailor was a small, good-looking, amusing, and merry sort of fellow.
He saw the shoemaker on the other side of the road and greeted him with a joke, but the
shoemaker did not like jokes and made a sour face and looked like.
and looked like fighting the tailor but the little fellow began to laugh and handed him his bottle saying
no harm men have a drink and swallow your rage the shoemaker took a big draft and suggested they
should walk on together all right so the tailor if you want to go to a town big town where there's
plenty of work the tailor always merry and fresh and red cheeks had no trouble getting work as well
as a kiss behind the door from the master's daughter and when he met the shoemaker he always had more
so fortunate that the tailor laughed and shared what he had with his companion.
When they had been sometime on the road, they came to a big forest through which
a way led to the king's city.
And there were two paths.
One took seven days and the other only two
and they didn't know which was which
and debated as to the quantity of bread they should take.
The shoemaker wanted to take enough bread for seven days
but the tailor was ready to take a risk and trust in God.
It was such a long way and the third day
the tailor had finished his bread
but the shoemaker had no pity on him.
By the fifth day the tailor was so hungry
he had asked the shoemaker for some bread.
For he was quite white and exhausted the shoemaker agreed and said that in exchange the tailor must put
Let him put out one of his eyes the unhappy tailor who didn't want to die
It could only agree and the heartless shoemaker cut out his right eye
The next day the tailor was again hungry and in the seventh day to excel exhausted to stand the shoemaker said that then you
That pity on him and give him more bread, but that in return he must have the tailor's other eye
Then the tailor begged God's forgiveness for the lighthearted way which he had lived and told the shoemaker that he had not
Deserved such treatment at his hands where he had always shared everything with him and without his eyes
He would not be able to sew and could only beg and he asked that he might not be left there to die alone in his blindness
But the shoemaker who had shut God out of his heart took his knife and cut out the left eye
Then gave the tailor a piece of bread cut him a stick and let him away when the Sun went down
They came out of the wood by some gallows, the shoemaker led the blind tailor there and left him,
worn out with pain and hunger. The tailor fell asleep and slept through the whole night.
When he woke up in the morning, he did not know where he was. On the gallows hung two poor sinners
and on the head of each set of crow. The two crows began to talk and one told the other that the dew
which during the night had fallen on them from the gallows would give back sight to anyone who
He took his handkerchief and soaked it in the dew in the grass, washed his eye sockets with it,
and had two healthy eyes. Soon the sun rose and the plain before him was the king's city,
with his beautiful gates and hundreds of towers. He distinguished every leaf on the trees and saw
the birds fly by and the midges dance in the air. He got out a needle and when he saw that he could
thread as well as ever his heart jumped for joy and he knelt and thanked God. Then he picked up
Soon he met a brown colt running about the field.
He seized it by the main.
He needs to jump on it and rode into town.
But the colt begged for its freedom, saying it was too young
and that even a light tailor would break its back
and let it be until it was strong enough.
And perhaps someday he'd be able to repay him.
So the tailor let the colt go.
But the tailor had not eaten since the previous day.
He then saw a stork and seized it by one of his legs, meaning he cut his head off so that he could have something to eat.
But the stork said that it was the holy bird which never harmed anybody and was a great use of the human race and begged to be allowed to live.
He told the tailor it would make it up to him another time, so the tailor let it fly away.
Then the tailor saw on the pond two little ducks. He caught one and wanted to ring the neck to have something to eat.
But the old duck swam out of the bushes and implored him to have pity on her dear children.
wanted to make an end of you.
So the good-tempered Taylor said that she should keep her
children and put the duck back in the water.
When he turned around, he saw an old hollow tree
where the bees flew in and out.
That will be my reward for my good deeds, he said.
But the queen bee came out and said,
if you touch my people and destroy my nest,
we will sting you with 10,000 glowing needles.
Leave us in peace and go your way.
In return, we will one day do you a service.
So the Taylor went away and came hungry into the town.
As it was midday, he entered an inn in eight, and since he looked for work and found a job,
he was a very good tailor.
He soon became famous, and everybody wanted a coat made by him.
And at last, he came to be an appointed court tailor.
But as it happens in life, on the same day, his old comrade made the court shoemaker.
and when the latter saw the tailor with two healthy eyes his conscience began to trouble him
and he planned to destroy the tailor before he could tell his story. So in the evening when
he had finished his work he went to the king and told him the tailor was the insolent fellow who had
boasted that he would find the golden crown which had been lost in the olden days. So the next
morning the king had the tailor brought to him and ordered him to produce the crown or leave the
The unhappy tailor packed up his bundle and prepared to leave the city, though he was
very sorry to leave the place where everything had gone so well.
When he came to the pond where he had met the ducks, there was the old duck cleaning
her beak at the bank.
The tailor told her what happened to him.
Is that all?
The duck, the crown fell in the water and is lying at the bottom of the pond.
Just lay your handkerchief on the bank, and then she dived down with her twelve children
and after five minutes came up again with the crown, lying on their wings and twelve
So the tailor wrapped up his handkerchief and took it to the king who gave him a golden chain as a reward
When the shoemaker saw that the plot had failed
He went again to the king and said that the tailor had boasted that he could produce a model of a royal castle and wax
With everything that was in it
It was uh
Somebody with my name on who's this
You type in the back to who you are
Oh, I know who's
What are you doing are you naked?
Okay, okay, okay, I'm gonna finish this story. Okay, I'll put on me. I'm gonna
Come back later. Okay. Anyway, I'm almost done with this story good guys gay. Okay, whatever. Okay. Okay, so
Okay, so
Okay, so here's about the gold okay, so then it says okay, so the tailor something things got worse
The king ordered the tailor to do that and said if there was even a nail missing the
tailor should be imprisoned in the earth for the rest of his life.
The tailor thought that things got worse.
And nobody could stand that, and again, he went his way.
But when he got to the hollow tree,
the queen bee flew out and asked him via the stiff neck.
Since he was hanging his head so low,
then the tailor told the story.
As the bees began to hum, and the queen bee said,
he must go home and come again tomorrow
at the same time with a big cloth.
When he arrived the next day,
the bees had made a perfect model.
The king was delighted and gave the tailor
a fine stone house.
but the shoemaker went a third time to the king and said that the tailor had boasted that he
could make a spring of water well up in the king's courtyard as high as the man and as clear as
crystal the tailor was ordered to do under pain of having his head cut off once more the tailor
prepared to leave with the tears running down his cheeks but the cult came running to him
and said he knew what he was to the matter.
The tailor must sit on his back.
He galloped through the courtyard and around it,
three times like lightning, and the third time,
drew himself down, and which time there was tremendous crash,
and a ball of earth flew up in the air
and over the castle, and immediately after,
water jetted as high as a man,
and hoarsed at his clearest crystal.
When the king saw it,
he embraced the tailor before everybody.
But the good luck again did not last.
The king had many daughters, one more beautiful than the other, but no son, and the wicked
shoemaker went once more to the king and said that the tailor had boasted that he could
bring the king a son through the air.
The king called the tailor and told him that within nine days he could bring him a son,
he could marry his eldest daughter, so the tailor went home and wondered what on earth
he could do.
Again, thinking nothing was to be done, he made up his bundle and went saying, I will
leave this place where I cannot live in peace.
But when he came to the meadow, his old friend the stork greeted him.
The stork said he should not grow any gray hairs over that, since he had long brought babies to town, and for once he could also fetch a little prince out of the well.
The tailor should go home and be quiet in nine days' time. He should go to court where the stork would come.
The tailor went home, and if the castle at the right time, the stork soon came knocking at the window.
The tailor opened the window, and then came the long legs walking carefully over the marble floor.
carrying in his beak a child like an angel,
his stretches little hands out to the queen.
The stork laid on her lap,
she was overjoyed at the tailor married the eldest daughter.
And the shoemaker had to make shoes
in which the tailor danced in at the wedding feast,
where after he was ordered to leave the city forever,
his row through the forest led to the gallows,
worn out with anger and the heat of the day,
he threw himself down.
And when he shed his eyes and wanted to sleep,
the two crows flew down with loud cries
and picked out his eyes.
He ran around like a crazy man in the wood and must have perished there for nobody ever heard or saw him again.
Good.
Tato had Harry.
It's a gaga, okay.
Audio books, was that good?
I think I have a, like, okay, reading voice.
I'm gonna get something out of, I'm gonna get my coffee out once again.
Or my, it's like a S'mores coffee.
Okay.
You're not aroused. Well, neither am I. That's good. It actually has some uh, it has some Bailey's cream in it
Okay
How about this is a book? This is an interesting book
How to stay sane in a fucked up world how about let's read a chapter of that
Something deeper than despair chapter one is I would not have this I would not have you to send into your own dreams
I would have you be a conscious citizen of this terrible and beautiful world
Ta-Nehisi Coates
On November 14, 2016, just six days after Donald Trump won the election, my wife Annie
woke up in the middle of the night in excruciating pain.
A trip to the ER revealed that the cancer she had been fighting for more than a year
had spread into her abdomen and a tumor was blocking her left kidney.
Several long hours later, she emerged from surgery with a plastic tube implanted in her
side and drained urine into a bag.
I was told she'd likely have three on this tube for the rest of her life.
When our three-year-old son visited, I would teach him not to touch mom's tube.
That was the moment I could hear despair calling me, almost audibly.
It said, your life is shit.
Everything is completely fucked.
Your best option is to go cower in the corner.
In that intense moment, I thought of the story I'd heard, the Vietnamese Buddhist monk and
peace activist, dick knocked on, tell countless times over the 20 years I studied with them.
One day, Thich Nhat Hanh was meditating in a jungle in Vietnam, and he saw a young banana tree with just three leaves.
The first leaf was fully grown, broad and flat in dark green.
The second leaf was still partially curled beneath the first, and the third leaf was buried like green and tender, just beginning to unfurl.
This was during the middle of the Vietnam War, and he was leading a huge organization of young people who'd help reveal villages that had been destroyed by bombs or napalm.
day with villagers whose lives had been ravaged by war and he witnessed the deaths of several of
his closest friends. The central question in his life at that moment was how to reconcile the
intensity of his calling to help suffering people with his mindfulness practice. He knew that he
needed his mindfulness practice to keep from being overwhelmed with despair, but how could he justify
cultivating peace and joy in himself while so many other people were dying?
He was holding this question in mind in looking at the young banana tree when he had a deep insight.
It occurred to him that the eldest banana leaf was fully enjoying her life as a leaf.
She was absorbing the sun and rain, radiating beauty and peacefulness.
However, she hadn't abandoned the other leaves to pursue her own happiness.
In fact, she had nourished herself fasting the sunshine.
She was also nourishing the younger leaves and banana tree and the entire jungle.
He decided that human beings were just like this.
As we nourish ourselves with peacefulness and joy, we're also supporting the well-being
of every other person in our lives.
In that hospital room, as I looked at my wife and son, I couldn't avoid seeing how much
they needed me.
They didn't need me to do anything in particular, they needed me to stay with them and help
them to see that they weren't alone, that life was still worth living.
If I could somehow find a way not to lose touch with what's beautiful and joyful in
life, if I could tap into something in me deeper than despair, then I'd have something
to offer the people I love most.
Deeper than despair. Looking around today is hard to escape the conclusion that our world is
Exquisitely fucked. Of course, there's a lot of beauty in this world at the same time
But the sheer magnitude of violence greed hatred and straight-up stupidity can be overwhelming if we let ourselves pay attention and care
The terrifying part for me is that what happens to good hearted people when we get overwhelmed by all of it
We're committed to paying attention and caring and we refuse to
escape into whatever privilege we can find. However, the intensity of suffering we experience
poisons us. We lose touch with our humanity. We either end up in despair on one side,
or we fall into toxic righteousness on the other.
Toxic righteousness is a term created by writer and activist Starhawk to describe the agri-fueled
self-certainty that pervades our political discourse. Toxic righteousness is what happens
when we're more mere inches from despair but somehow summon enough strength to lash out
instead of collapsing. In that state we're incapable of listening and often don't see why we should
since our opponents are less than human.
If anyone tries to say that our vitriol and indignation aren't helping, we get violently
defensive because we believe the only alternative is giving up entirely.
The challenge of staying human in a fucked up world comes down to how we respond to the
immensity of suffering that confronts us from every direction.
Whether I'm suffering from things in my own life, things in the lives of people I love
or the pain I feel when I pay attention to the conditions in our world, and it's usually
what all of those, I have to find a way to take care of the compassion in me so that
I don't end up overwhelmed.
If I can't, I'll find myself in total despair, possessed by toxic righteousness, or worst
I'll find whatever little bubble of privilege I can to escape into and stop caring.
Once I understand the suffering in the world can turn me to someone I don't want to be,
I became extremely motivated to find a way to stay human.
I don't want to stop caring as I don't want to drown in anger and bitterness.
I want to stay present and be a force for good.
I want to become thick-knocked Hans Badana Leaf with enough joy and peace that I'm able
to benefit myself and others.
I refuse to let everything that's fucked up in the world strip me of my humanity.
From here to there. How do I become that kind of person? How do I strengthen that capacity in me?
What am I supposed to do if it's not easy for me?
What if I really struggle with anger despair and shutting down? Is it possible to change?
I can almost guarantee that when I was first exposed to mindfulness and passion trading as a 19-year-old college student
I was a much more fucked up person than you are. I grew up poor in Boston with an alcoholic single mother
I was constantly bullied hopeless as a teenager
I never knew my father by the time I got to college.
I was angry and lonely and had a few social skills.
When a political science professor of mine assigned pieces
of every step by Thich Nhat Hanh to change everything,
I immediately recognized that mindfulness and compassion
were exactly what were missing from my life.
Then as a 19-year-old sometimes do when they find something
that makes sense to them, I immersed myself in these practices
often spending several months on retreat with Thich Nhat Hanh
every year following him wherever he went.
Through all the practice and study, I've learned to experience more joy and freedom than I would ever thought possible.
I've gone from being someone with an intense amount of suffering and self-destructiveness to someone with real intimacy and harmony in my life.
If I can change anybody, Cam, nothing is free until it is.
On the other hand, change isn't easy, and it doesn't happen on its own.
It requires that we find ideas of practices that make sense to us on a deeper level.
We have to engage with those ideas and allow them to change how we see the world.
Then we have to put them in practice and see the effects they produce in our lives.
Finally, when we find a teaching or training that feels truly helpful, we must commit ourselves
to deliberate practice.
The more time and effort we invest, the greater the change we can expect to see.
The practice is an idea as we used to require so much effort to begin to feel like second nature.
It is as if you put so much energy into learning to speak French,
then all of a sudden you realize you developed a little fluency.
You can now have a conversation in French without much effort at all.
In this case, you start to experience a compassionate thought arising on its own
in a moment that would have triggered anger in the past.
It's the fruit of our dedication.
It's the effort that leads to effortlessness.
Words get sick.
It's possible to pay attention and care about the suffering in the world without letting
it poison us.
There is a quality of mind we can develop that allows us to stay present with suffering
without losing touch with the joy of being alive.
We can accept that pain that I've been a part of life without letting that make us callous
or uncaring.
Instead, we can respond with radical acceptance and a willingness to do whatever we can to
alleviate suffering.
The word that my teacher, ThickKnockedOn, used to describe this way of relating to life was mindfulness.
However, I don't really like that word. Too many people use it to mean something entirely different from what ThickKnockedOn means.
They say that mindfulness is about taking deep breaths, sitting on a cushion on the floor, or watching your thoughts and feelings with disinterest, like you're watching a boring TV show.
When Thich Nhat Hanh is the word mindfulness, he's describing a way of relating to the world and specifically the suffering that contains compassion, joy, equanimity, and wisdom.
It is precisely the quality that allows us to stay human in fucked up situations, to stay open, caring, and able to relate.
It's possible for words to get sick and lose their meaning.
When that happens, we can either abandon the word or we can try to rehabilitate it.
I'm not entirely ready to give up on the word mindfulness, at least not today.
But when I use it, remember I mean to use it in a deeper sense.
Regardless of what you want to call it,
this ability to stay human in the face of intense suffering
is something that's in short supply in our world.
It's also something that we desperately need.
So the next question is how to develop the capacity
in ourselves.
How can we learn to do this better?
I spent my life studying this question,
and I've come to believe that it can be developed
through training ourselves in a set of specific skills.
This book is designed to help you develop the skills
that will help you stay human, help you pay attention,
care deeply, and feel connected,
even in really fucked up situations.
First, you'll learn about each skill,
then you'll try it out until you find a way
of using it that feels beneficial.
Finally, you'll practice it until it feels natural.
There we go.
How are we doing?
What God do you say?
Dumb cluck, guidey, and gay, at least he's sitting in a tree. Hold on.
Psyche's awakening, wink, wink.
It's an autobiography.
No, it's not, but I mean, it's that I did study, I did study Buddhism,
interestingly, and that did teach me a lot about the nature of suffering all through the world. I
do believe we can be better people. I believe that we can improve. I believe that
the world is fucked up sometimes, but
It's how we react to situations not the situations that that really make us right
And also I like how we talk about mindfulness it's like because some people yeah mindfulness is about just being aware of
Like more than just ourselves and our desires are what's to have like
be less selfish, so that's interesting.
So guys, is anybody on TikTok?
Cause I'm on TikTok, I'll put my link.
I'll try to put my link in this thing.
Let me see if I can find the,
if you're on it, like there's,
I haven't signed a lot of people on it,
but I'm almost, I'm at 250 subscribers or members, right?
Or like whatever I'm subscribed, right?
And then
I need 1,000 and I can be it up.
I'm on one tonight.
You are.
No, you won't.
I won't kick you.
No, I won't.
So anyway, I just opened TikTok and look what it says.
No matter what is going on in your life. Don't quit no matter what obstacles you face or the heartache you feel
Don't give up someone is praying for you and you will make it through you're my prayers and God is on your side
Amen. Oh, it's very nice. Oh
Yeah, this lady has some pretty good quotes
The road I have traveled has not always been an easy one and the path was often full of stones,
but I am still here. I know that the only reason I was able to make it this far,
the only reason I'm here today is the fact that God was walking the road with me every step of the
way. Amen. Promise yourself, no matter how bad people treat you, never become a bad person to
Sometimes you just have to play the role of the fool to fool the fool who thinks they are fooling you
When the train goes through a tunnel and it gets dark you don't throw away the ticket and jump off
You sit and trust the engineer trust God today no matter how dark your situation God says you are coming out and
Then it says what does this say?
You can go 40 days without food three days without water eight minutes without air, but you can't go a single second without God
When you have a good heart you help too much you trust too much you give too much you love too much
And it seems like you're the one who gets hurt the most
right
Nice
Well come on where's everybody 23 people in chat I'm just like you know I wanted
We and when summer gets here if she wants to start a panel, I mean she wants me to start a panel
I will or someone can sponsor it
but
What's wrong Goddy?
This is really good. This is Moors no shake with it with the Bailey's of it
I added a coffee to it like a Vietnamese coffee. Hey tricks no they
There's the link yeah
Okay, what kind of dog is pristine's dog
You know what kind of dog that is because I kept trying to like I was like I thought I put a cock a poo
And I put a multi-poo and they they both like the multi-poo looks
Way too small and the cock a poo
Labrador, okay
Guys, I'll be right back. Let me see. I'll play I'll play my song. I'll play my I'll play my thing again. Hold on my video
We're back. I mean, I'm just gonna make the I mean makes it for see. Oh, oh, hold on. Never mind. Never mind. Hello
Go see hello, can you hear me brother? Hi? Yes, sir
How are you? I think it's a I think it's a golden retriever, isn't it?
No, it's a lab or doodle.
I mean, it's like a part lab, part poodle.
It's like, it has that curly hair,
you know, beautiful curly hair.
is it
My mother owns a
It's Husky and Pomeranian
It's kind of expensive actually
Pomsky or some shit Pomsky. Yeah. Um, so basically it's like literally like it's a miniature of
Small oh
Yeah
Cuz it's so little though. I mean it's fine
Yeah, but the cute dog. I love like little dogs. They're like, you know, sometimes they're like a little bit, you know
And it doesn't even like how our talk like a husky does
No
Well, yeah, but that was my school a mascot was a husky
I was there for seven years ship. It's a fighting house. Yeah. Yeah
We have big basketball team at my school, but nice. That's it. Yep
So, yeah, we were that's lucky. So what happened? That's not on beat us. Did you go to be this channel?
Last night, did you go to beat us? I heard you went to beat us and it didn't go well
Hello who me yeah
I don't think I did I don't well, I don't remember the last time I joined her panel was like a month ago or like
and
She said you went over there last all she did was walk me. I don't know. Maybe I did
Christine said you went over there she answered the phone you called her a bitch and then she hung up on you
No, but you know I probably did last time I talked here at all she did well cuz she was talking shit to you remember
Yeah, yeah
She was she was she wasn't talking to me really but it was like her chat was a little bit but not her
Wow chat was
Yeah, the chat was a little bit. She was fine, you know, I did actually join her panel one time just like
Hang out and have a conversation, but all she did was like kick people out
Well, it wasn't it wasn't just me obviously. It was like like everyone that joined besides the one dude up there
Well, well, I'm glad you you sound good tonight. It's not like you're a little bit sober tonight. I'm just having a
celebration last night
Me too, but we had fun last night. It was a fun night and
I haven't fun today. Look. Let me see it. I got another
Me need some more cards coming as yet my shirt. I showed you my shirt
Haven't seen it brother. Okay
Is that a picture of you with your cat? Yeah, it's me. Just kidding. I do like it though. Thank you
That's good. It does look like me out. Basically basically a skeleton with like a thin layer of skin
But it's okay
Hop up here. I thought so too. Well, yeah, but yeah, it's actually like
He might he said he wasn't going to he said he was fine
City in the chat
Yeah, so I looked at tick-tock and it seems like it's like a bunch of people selling like but like everyone's like trying to sell their
Like their goods like they have like they have to be like a tick-tock shop
And like a lot of people were like selling up like the shirt. Thank you. Yeah on Timu. It's a really nice quality
I'm really impressed with Timu for like most of the stuff
They're like pretty fast and the guy in the shirt is a little too, yeah, he's a little bit too jacked to meet me, right?
Pretty funny
So let's see one second
You say summer was coming here or would you say earlier? Well, it's a summer. Oh, it's summer has a she has a panel coming
You know, she hasn't come redeemed hers yet. And so
Whenever she whenever she wants to come and do hers
We will do hers, but I think she asked me to wait and do hers until she's like here
Yeah, yeah, so
Yeah, so I had you be nice day
Do you see you see any of there?
Did you see any of the earlier show it would be a Chris K give?
Did a reading with pristine?
Anybody see that nice pretty I did not brother. I was on
I
Was watching I'm not good F and F
My earning I was watching that earlier
FNS, what is that?
Fresh and fit, but I okay weekend so I didn't watch anything. Yeah, so I was catching up on it today
Yep, I've heard of I was watching his street. I was watching his street debate. Oh
Yeah, well cool. Okay
Okay, so let me see you somebody in PayPal. Okay, so okay
Yeah, she's a babe. Let's see how mature you are. So yeah Sebastian Sebastian. What's Sebastian saying?
Oh, there's the old Taco Bell.
So why would I say checking out PayPal?
I don't know.
I don't remember why.
I thought I was gonna do something on PayPal.
I forgot though.
Oh, maybe I'm sharing my link.
Hold on.
So you're watching videos,
you don't know what you're talking about.
Sebastian, watch your mouth in the comments here.
You see, are you really having Sebastian?
Come on.
Be nice, Sebastian.
the
you're like, oh, yeah. Oh, JT. You're the only guy without the wrench. You know, Sebastian doesn't have a wrench and I joined the most.
I had a wrench one time. Very, very long time ago.
Yeah, a wrench is like, okay.
And you literally, you literally just, you literally gave it out to everybody in chat that night, by the way.
I forget what it, I forget why you did it, but you literally just gave everyone a wrench.
I was just drunk. I was drunk. I should not have done that. That was an accident.
Actually, I think you were like arguing with someone and I had you back and I was like, yeah, I agree.
And you were like, hey, do you want a wrench?
And then we had, after that, it was, I don't know how long ago, it was, we had a, we were talking about Taro,
and then we obviously were arguing about it.
And he took it away.
Then you remember, I was like, give me back my wrench.
Yep. Okay guys, I have a little surprise for the chat. Here you go guys
We'll do another one of these
Haven't it's a feeling very generous lady because you guys have been so generous. So here you go
Let's see you got it
Congratulations to you
Who is it the oceans woo? Yeah, I know who it is the oceans deep woo. Yeah, she's been on the show before she's a
Psychic on YouTube as well
And she's really cool. Okay, so goddess here. Okay. Hold on a second
You guys were having one on one time. That's why I didn't come up here
Well, it was before I had him on and now we're having one on one time again
You're welcome
Yeah, it's wrong like to open the panel up. You can sponsor the panel. Otherwise, I'll just do the one-on-one for now
Hey, Gotti, how are you? I'm good pal. How are you day going? Why are you talking like like you have like, you know a severe I
Had some stroke. I was in the sun too long today and I got a little burnt now. I gotta talk like this
You sound like
He said like you're like, you know, like a prep school a prep school student
I don't know if they can the white equivalent of Urkel
No, no, no, I would not I would not well that'd be that'd be like that'd be like, you know, it'd be crazy of me
the
Well
Yeah
When it was like God he's down. They did not mean that
That's good to make fun of the handicapper
Sometimes
As long as you're not going down on yourself. I mean shit. You're already doing better
God you're terrible. You're terrible
I'm the worst the worst the very worst
Yeah, you want to slow-mo? Yeah, yeah, he pulls his he pulls us you're just kidding
There's love you can hear Liz when I do my baby talk. Oh my god. She loves that
She loves that dude, you should hear
That's what we do because the women love to hear the Google Gaga because they're always saying it
Hey, if you like
They got Lady Gaga
If you hold up the lighter right and you light it and then you spray the Febreze will it do like a flame?
No, oh, did they stop doing that?
I don't think it's like I don't think it's like a real aerosol. It says it says it's not aerosol
It says no, no, it says no it says no flammable propellants. No
No formaldehyde and no dyes with a
Corn derived odor fighter. So it's the odor fighters corn derived. It's not a strange corn. That is water-based formula
at the age of seven I'm running around the neighborhood with a fucking flamethrower basically just fucking burning anything I could find with that thing
Hey mom, you with the anarchist cookbook at like 10 years old
Ants, look out Ants, here comes the fucking napalm
Hey babe, welcome
Oh she's got the cherries out today, ooh look at that
Hey daddy, is that your daughter?
Yeah that's me, that's me, yeah yeah that's, no that's my mommy
Oh, but she's called you. Oh, she knows the daddy. Yeah, mommy daddy. Mommy daddy. Are you married or is that just your sex sexual partner?
That's my sexual partner
Okay, interesting
What is it? Oh, it's a woman. It's a woman. Yeah, it's a woman. Oh my god. I'm shocked. Oh my god
The pale open guy, thank you
Go pose through again
Yeah, thank you ghost for
This guy's really a champ dude. He's really redeemed himself
Yes, he did he always does here. I'll bring him back. What's that right?
That's about doing your banner for you this one. He's given like over a hundred bucks so far
Can you put some ghost emojis in the chat?
It's one of the members, it's under the member emojis.
There's a ghost emoji, you know,
just like you can just share, just put ghost, yay.
Supposedly the open panel open and sale,
so let's say I'll do it, close one, close one,
one, two, three o'clock, three a.m.
Or in, no, okay, three a.m.
Okay, that'll be our final panel today.
There we go.
Thank you, ghost.
Go on Ray, everybody's gonna come up.
Come on, fill it up.
10 people at least, right?
Yeah
Ten people. Yeah, I can have ten people and I'm gonna change the color of this right now to something ghosts would like
Let me see. He'll probably like
There that green
Let's do it
Okay, come on up. Anybody want to come up? Oh, yeah, and I'll put that there. Oh, there we go
There's a ghost. Oh, yeah, Jamie got some ghost emoji. It's a different ghost, but yeah, it's a ghost emoji too. That works
It's pinned
Because I just fucking I okay, I just fucking pee my pants goes
Because you scared of it with that noise
Getting this party started
He's got the prison
It's a horse tail a pony tail a pony tail. Yeah, why are you being mean to people in the comments for somebody said?
What did I say?
Don't know forget them. They're down there. We're up here spot. Can you do a little flex for well, they can we can have
Yeah, yeah, yeah, look at those guns. Whoa
Again
Like I said, I'm gonna do like I said up. I'm gonna put God you get a car
You're gonna be in my new deck and ghost will be my new deck and and spunk
You're gonna be the death card gaudy. Yeah, I'm the death card. Yeah, I'll make gaudy the death card. I'll just
Yeah, you can be in the you can be on a car with God is it goes like walking around in the back
You can both you can both be walking together side by side. No, you can make those the six of cups
Okay, six of cups. So that's yeah nostalgia. Okay. I'll do that one
You know, but my ghost is like, you know, this goes in his 20s when you're back in having your wild college days
I'm nice
Little Gotti little Gotti
I know what he wants. I know what he wants. And I kind of paid this that kind of habit
I know he wants though. He wants me to crash on you
And you kind of deserve it to be honest with you, but I'm not gonna do it tonight. We're not doing
I'm asking nicely Gotti
No, so me and go ghost. You're the man tonight, dude. You went praising you tonight is ghost night
Go see I'm not gonna like you just like open up the panel. You know, you're the hero. Yes, sir
Yeah
So everyone's happy summer shoes
Summer said that she wanted to do hers when she's here and so she said to save her when she's here and it says that so I was like
Yeah, so she's you know, she might be here tonight a little bit later
But I'll I can I'll run hers whenever she wants. So we're good
Fucking what what was going on here? Yeah, what you're freaked out about can you tell me?
No, there's just some put some people whispering in the room
Listening again, buddy, you know that the chat is like it's a silent Chad people are typing words
They think it's not saying things give that give yours on like the if you're here
You were talking to him nobody cares about Sebastian. You were he told me to get you. He told me to get you
It's not cool
He doesn't have to be retargeted because it's canadian
I don't give a fuck. There are there are a couple smart canadian brethren. He might be one of them
I don't know man. Sebastian once bought a mattress and he took it on a public bus to get it home
You know the product would be on you
That is crazy
You give me some Bob burn his ass up right now because I had to pay to open the panel
If you should have paid to open it up and let me talk to him
You doesn't need therapy
Who I do
You imagine you imagine ghosts being somebody's therapist
Yeah, I mean, I don't think they would be a good therapist. They'd actually work out pretty good. You would you like to know how it would go?
Yeah, they wouldn't be you know, jump off a building the first night
I'm not gonna go that far. We're gonna keep it. Okay. It's it's we're gonna keep it
This world's not worth it. He was about the office window. No, I'm just kidding. No, that won't happen
That's what I would do if you go through my second hand.
I'm really hard to be professional at work
because I have these like really intrusive thoughts
that'll be like, just tell them to do it.
Oh, terrible.
Oh, shit.
It's been dark.
Did we just go that way?
Yeah, but it's like, it's like a different thing, my bad.
OK, I don't need a dark thought, Spucky,
but that is really pretty kind of evil.
I knew it.
They don't come out.
Like, they never come out.
But you can't help it.
It's intrusive.
It's like, you don't think it.
It's like, they just force it away.
Yeah, they force it away.
You don't want to think it.
I only think darker would be like
You're just like
You'd show them how to do it
You're going like 70 on the highway and you just like do a u-turn just you how do you feel about yellow?
Cuz yellow means go
It's slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow down slow
I mean my mother made a great debate why I shouldn't drive a motorcycle, but I'll say I'm gonna do what I want
But now I'm thinking maybe I got my debates. Oh, well, I'm not even good debater
But now I think the lawyer is my debates because of her
Well, maybe maybe you learn after you learn from what your mom maybe maybe yeah, you inherited that skill pretty good
Bringsick can you give her a prescription for something?
Smoky, don't smile when you say that when you make it. Come on. We've heard it a thousand times. I don't smile when you say it
right
I can't Goddy. She has to be my patient. You must have something there
Yeah, I'm gonna pay to kick you out of my own panel. She has to admit my own open
Hold on. Let me get a glass of you ever have the media. You know what happens once you get in there for the best of them
You know I'm saying something so I don't you know, I'm not I'm not like
Why does it turn green
I don't hear about green green green
Can you please explain to us I think every young woman should hear that you shouldn't be a you shouldn't be discussing horror because
But then I have to give this whole lecture and usually it's in front of their parent too, so it's really awesome. Oh my god
Yes, Billy said to pick his nose
You can pick your nose if you can't friends, but you can't pick your friends nose
You should
Sebastian tell me
They're picking on each other
He has mental illness
I don't question Sebastian. I let him do what he wants
Should I ask Sebastian what was his problem, and then I'll come back to you. I mean you could
Why was he calling you up for it? Is he just recording? I mean, I don't understand it. Oh, no, it's a little sticky
I know you've got a 40% off limbo suction thing and
If you need somebody to talk for hours Sebastian's a man
Don't I don't I don't if you need a hit-and-run. I'll be up here. Okay. I'm pretty sure he said
I don't kind of make the argument real quick real quick, and I don't want to actually debate it
You know open panel, but I'm pretty sure he said you were a fake-ass comedian
You're not funny even when you're trying to be funny. You know what I would have to agree with them
I that was his only argument. I would agree. I can't disagree with any of that
Okay, I think your buddy
I'm pretty sure that's what he wanted to tell you
It's like you ever see the movie porkies is that type of humor?
Yeah
What 80s dumb dumb. Yeah, they're really terrible. It's really bad sex movie. They're great sex movies
Yeah, it doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. Yes earmatters
The the sex sexual conduct matters at all matters. How does it not matter?
That was a stupid ass question to be honest.
Great fucking movies.
That wasn't a great movie. How was that?
And how were you funny by the way?
Actually now that I'm thinking about how are you funny sir?
You tried to be funny but you're not.
Well have you ever seen him? It's hilarious.
Say a joke, say a joke.
Have I ever seen him that's hilarious.
You know what Spunky? That was a good fucking one.
Spunky got it. I'll give you that one.
You want to have a good laugh? I'll show you my face. Hold on
The one that fucking wanted this fashion look at my expression oh
Beautiful
I
Baby laughs
You don't make a joke you don't the fuck you're talking about you too stupid to have the conversation any every time we ever
Eh, you ever you're not you're not on my level you realize that right? Oh, of course not
I'm way up in the heaven. So you better stick to the you better go back to the comments stick to them
Because that's the only people you ever talk shit. Are you kicking me off the panel that you paid for?
No, sir, you you're allowed to be up here. It's free speech as long as it's not my panel
It's like the channel dumb fucks. So why don't you ask him?
But you're not on my level you never want to do it. See I just let him go
Yeah, you just
It's like let us assume let us assume that you've gotten a fight with a UFC fighter
What are you gonna do beat them up? No, you're not gonna be done
Sebastian's here. Hold on. Yeah, let's run that bitch. Welcome. I'm still gonna whoop your ass by the way. All right, wait your turn
I ain't gonna wait nothing bitch
I'm gonna let this guy this goes guy handle you for now. No, no go ahead. I'm not JT you dumb
That's all right. Let me I'm still having my conversation, but he said I don't know if you understood what you just said
Oh, yeah, it's true. He's not funny whatsoever. He tries to be funny
He wants to over tries to be funny not like he laughs like it's funny. She had funny jokes monkey was actually funny
You're not funny at all. Exactly. You're not a good debater. You're not a good conversationer. You're not
You're definitely not a fucking comedian. Is this
How's it going Stephanie?
God he's allowed to run his mouth and not get checked tonight because you get to see a Patrick
That is a hill please not for my mommy. Mommy. Yeah
Your mommy should race
How horrible
For mommy
I already opened the panel up for you. Let me know how hard you want me to go because I got a good job
Good job. I'm sponsoring the panel. That's very good. Yeah. That was nice. Thank you
Yes, thank you very much. You're awesome. There goes. Yeah, okay. We thank them. That's enough. Thanks. Yeah
I myself
What do you want us to make you a fucking lasagna smashing get at that boy?
Already under investigation for several crimes who doesn't love a good lasagna
your non-existent wife, I mean are you asking me a ghost this Goddy guy
He's under investigation for several crimes. He's committed. I believe it
Oh, yeah, what do they find oh, they've got you on many charges a Goddy
He already knows what he's being a
was being charged with but I don't know what Spongebob
Spongebob
Yeah
What does tie mean tie like tie what means thank you for your
Fuck you understand it. This is like five
Thank you for your argument now we can flip it and show it the people you're heard
Thank God
Summer, you know what I heard about you, Summer?
Check this out, Goddy, Goddy, Goddy, check this out.
Summer, guess what I heard about you?
You passed out at a fucking concert
and fucking you woke up to summer.
When I fell asleep to the hard one in the metal concert
Listen, I fell asleep
To fucking stat. Oh, dude. I fell asleep to static X man, and I couldn't believe
The last man plays you fucking pass out man. You know to be like
Dude summer summer summer I relate to you like for real I dude my people had to fucking walk me to my fucking car
I couldn't even drive it
And then they said that I was gonna come here later
They said that a hold on a minute, dude
Then they said that I fucking even tried to get water out of my fucking like tire like I was at a water
I
Said was I step in your toes. You're supposed to have a panel
I paid for a panel tonight and I asked him I was like she's not coming up here
Or I didn't think you were and now you're here. So now I feel like I'm stepping in your toes. That's all I said
You paid for a panel tonight
Yeah, sir, do you would you like to double-check it the burden or please on me? Would you like me?
I was never a I was never maybe you should have shut the fuck up and stop talking
Like I said, did I pay for a panel tonight or not?
The one of the panels right here just ask him
Look
I was in I was in the military and and I was an NC. I don't give a fuck
How does that mean that means you don't that no no no that means you don't call us a sir
Maybe you should pretend maybe you should protect God even I don't give a fuck what you were. Why would I care?
Yeah, don't call me a sir. We always said sir
Okay, ma'am
Man, you're a real disrespectful, aren't you? Wow. How am I disrespectful?
Don't tell me not to call you something when I'm calling you fucking sir. Are you not a sir?
I'll give a fuck where you were. I'm not calling me sergeant.
How are you doing, sweetie?
I'll call you sergeant. Would you like me to call you sergeant, sir?
I will call you that from now on.
Summer, I'm doing better.
Awesome, awesome.
I'm doing good, beautiful.
You sound great. Oh summer. How'd they go in summer?
Summer sounds real good. Yeah, and spunky sounds good too. Yeah
I didn't scare off. I gave her a 40% discount
Maybe she pressed wrong button on her phone do that again funky the home alone face
Do it, yeah, yeah, yeah
What's the tattoo? What's the tattoo on the right arm? What is that?
This one. Yeah, it's a goat. Oh
By the way, by the way, Sebastian you handle all your shit. That's the reason why I opened it up for God
I didn't feel like talking but I decided to go on the pillow anyways
Yeah, you handle your shit. Did you fill any other kind of girl? Oh, yeah, I can handle this gunk this punk gotty any time
Summer's backstage. Yeah, fuck Ziggy. Who cares who cares Ziggy's an idiot. Trust me. I've done for a lot of time
Okay, the whole reason why I paid for Sebastian handles business did you handle it?
Yeah, you got a bathroom at 10. Is that what I can handle any one of these bunks you heard
Hello summer
Don't come at fashion anymore at all
Talk about that you don't fuck you're talking about it. There's a million different colors, and it's really cool in detail
But I got your back fashion
So that's awesome. Goals. I appreciate it. Goat farm. Oh, you must have a goat for our little goats. They do the little thing
This one
I love goat
It's funny Sebastian when I don't want to talk to you, right?
My ex-girlfriend was not able to handle it summer by the way summer but they don't remember when Slayer would come out and they'd be like
Those are not able to handle real men like us
Well, why would you make fun of the man?
This is the kind of man that holds when a real man gets from before I can't believe the test
Hey, I'd be thanking you for sponsoring the panel of anything
Listen to everyone even summer
I'm not trying to be rude there, but you're not going to pull me
I'll do whatever I want here. No, I'll never get one. Well, you're not going to silly Sebastian
Know that so shut the fuck up
You shut the fuck up, why are you here?
Hey Stephanie, I sent a cash objective so you can it bounced
Bank of America check bounced
Well, that shit ain't gonna check out a summer if I pay for we go to their house and just beat the shit out of each one of them
100% summer how much can you
Summer and they'll know that a bunch of
I've seen your video summer you
You think you're stronger than Stephanie took a ship
Some of you think you're stronger than spunky
Me and her I ain't go fight we go play boobies together. What you talking about?
Yeah
I
Of course not
Your boys you said you paid for a fucking panel man, that's kind of corny
Thank you. You buy off your farm yet or what? How's that corny dumb fuck? How's that corny explain?
How's it corny? No, no no stock. How is it corny? How's it corny?
You're a dumb fucking bitch likes to show your tears nobody wants to see it. I'm talking to him
How's it corny?
Oh, I definitely want to see you.
They'll be out here.
Can I talk to you?
Talk to us.
Can you talk to whoever you are?
We can't talk.
No, I guess you know how I felt the other night when I paid for a fucking panel and you were a bitch
Nobody gets a fuck about you either bitch. No one gets a fuck.
You're a pussy.
Okay, cool.
Talk to her like that.
You're talking to a woman. Remember that?
Fuck you and her. How about that?
She's the pussy that Debussy's pussy.
Exactly. That's why I talked to her.
I should pay for a panel and it should be one versus six.
Oh, the problem is that you should not be here.
For so you don't get it off you dumb fuck pussy. Yeah, fuck him up
Think about it
huh
This doesn't pay homage to ghost hour
Yeah, I think I wish to go fuck did I pay for it?
Yeah, you fell you fell
Hey, honest to psyching his cats
Oh, there he is. There he is.
What are you doing there?
He's muted. You're muted.
You're muted. Nobody gives a fuck
summer. You don't fuck, you know.
What are you doing, man?
For three hours.
paid money and nobody was gonna talk shit to you.
Where the fuck do you think you at, dummy?
Guys, can you hear me now? Can you hear me now?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay.
I created a tarot card.
For Santa, it's the inspiration for this one,
but I need to work on it a little bit.
It doesn't quite look like I need maybe a picture of her,
but here, how's that look?
I don't know what he's talking about.
That's a nice dog.
Oh
What do you guys do to Sebastian? Oh nice to hear
Sebastian watch this stay in the chat by the way say there. Oh, yeah
My heart goes out to all the tattooed women. I love them
Oh, that's so sweet.
Fuck that dog.
What?
What's wrong with the dog?
The dog fags.
The dog's awesome.
Exactly that's what I'm saying biggie. Did you sell your chicken farm yet?
Your drunk right now good. I'm good. No, I'm not drunk at all when you're high on drugs
You're not on a present sober I've never seen you sober once. Hey digger you vaccinated. I
Am not vaccinated fucking wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Are you talking about COVID?
I can't say that word. Oh, okay. Don't say that. Don't say that. Sorry. Sorry. CB cannot say CB. Yeah. Yeah, you can say
Incredible
Happens
Oh my god, that's awesome. Go. It's awesome. You're dropping a wad on site this week
Your neck
Yeah, yeah, but let me know it's for but I'll be I'm gonna reset the panel. We're right back everybody. We're right back